♪ Blink blink blink WoW! ♫
♪ Tickle tickle tickle WoW! ♫
♪ Surprise surprise surprise WoW! ♫
♪ WoW, WoW! ♫
♪ Blink blink blink WoW! ♫
♪ Tickle tickle tickle WoW! ♫
♪ Surprise surprise surprise WoW! ♫
♪ WoW, WoW! ♫
♪ Something was in my eyes, don't misunderstand it for a wink ♫
♪In that moment our distance will disappear ♫
♪ Love is a special two-dimension ♫
♪ A mystery with an unknown depth ♫
♪ All the things I thought of seemed like would all come true ♫
♪ But love is a strange dimension ♫
♪ A story that will smudge with tears ♫
♪ Though I wanna hold your hand ♫
♪ Blink blink blink WoW! ♫
♪ Tickle tickle tickle WoW! ♫
♪ Surprise surprise surprise WoW! ♫
♪ WoW WoW! ♫
♪ Blink blink blink WoW! ♫
♪ Tickle tickle tickle WoW! ♫
♪ Surprise surprise surprise WoW! ♫
♪ WoW WoW! ♫
♪ The sun was in my eyes, don’t misunderstand it for a wink ♫
♪ In that moment, reality will disappear ♫
♪ Love is a special two-dimension ♫
♪ A mystery without a shadow ♫
♪ All the things I thought of seemed like they would all come true ♫
♪ But love is a strange dimension ♫
♪ Pages will turn with the wind ♫
♪ Although I want you to hear my voice ♫
♪ She she she she’s pretty, she’s pretty ♫
♪ She’s pretty, she’s pretty ♫
♪ I don’t know, I don’t know, my cheeks are getting red ♫
♪ She's pretty, she's pretty ♫
♪ She’s pretty, she’s pretty ♫
♪ I want you to hear my voice ♫
♪ Though you can’t hear it ♫
♪ Though it can’t reach you ♫
♪ I will put my heart in this balloon ♫
♪ Here, pop! There, pop!
Pop! Pop! Pop! ♫
♪ If I fold my heart and let it stand ♫
♪ It’ll go past this dimension ♫
♪ Little by little, into your world ♫
♪ Love is a special two-dimension ♫
♪ A mystery with an unknown depth ♫
♪ All the things I thought of seemed like they would all come true ♫
♪ But love is a strange dimension ♫
♪ A story that will smudge with tears ♫
♪ Though I wanna hold your hand ♫
♪ She she she she’s pretty, she’s pretty ♫
♪ She's pretty, she's pretty ♫
♪ I don’t know, I don’t know, my cheeks are getting red ♫
♪ I wanna hold your hand ♫
♪ Blink blink blink WoW! ♫
♪ Tickle tickle tickle WoW! ♫
♪ Surprise surprise surprise WoW! ♫
♪ WoW WoW! ♫
A lot of you are here at our second concert [ALWAYZ]
Let us first say hello, two, three...
Hello, we are LOVELYZ.
Hello!
Hello, I'm JiAe of LOVELYZ.
Hello, I'm JIN of LOVELYZ.
Everyone, I've missed you.
I'm YeIn.
Everyone, I really really missed you. I'm JiSoo.
Everyone, I really really really missed you. I'm MiJoo.
Everyone, it's good to see you. I'm SuJeong.
Hello, I'm Leader Baby Soul.
Hello, I'm Flower Kei.
What's different from yesterday is that we're filming a DVD today.
Oh, oh, scream!!
So we will appreciate it if you enjoy yourselves
and help us to make a good film.
Fighting!
The heat is high since more of you are here today than yesterday.
Thank you.
You're the best!
Just like yesterday, the first appearance
is the most nervous part
Right, unnies?
I was really nervous.
Did you sleep well? YES!!!
Because I had a very exciting concert
with LOVELINUS yesterday,
I had a good dream.
- What was it?
- What was it about?
- Did you really dream?
- What was the dream about?
I had a dream that made me feel so good.
Oh, really?
Of course.
Tell us, tell us, tell us.
- I think we'll hit the jackpot.
- You want me to tell?
You shouldn't talk about your dreams!
You can say it a day after.
Then, I'll tell you tomorrow.
I couldn't sleep yesterday.
But I came here today and
energized myself with food.
And I'm here to enjoy despite the hotness.
Then shall we make a powerful stage
with LOVELINUS today?
YES!
There are so many of you here.
When the courtains fell down,
I couldn't hide my happiness.
- It's so nice to meet you!
- Nice to meet you!
Is there anyone who came yesterday?
YES!!
Then, who came for the first time today?
Hello~~
For the first comers here,
do you know the title of our concert?
ALWAYZ!!
Please, explain the meaning of the concert title, Baby Soul.
Our concert...
She's putting it up on me.
Our concert title is 'ALWAYZ',
was made up from ALWAYS and LOVELYZ.
That's why it's 'ALWAYZ'.
It means that we will be always with you.
I like it so much.
I'm fluttered.
Did you like the opening clip?
YES!!
Did you like it?
YES!!!
We had a promise ceremony at the opening clip.
- That's right.
You promise that you'll join our clip next time, right?
All of you should come together next time.
The atmosphere is really hot from the beginning.
- It's hot, hot!
- I really like it.
So let's make an historical concert today.
We, LOVELYZ, have prepared lots of things
for LOVELINUS today, right?
Right, right.
You can expect a better stage following
'Lovelyz in Winterland'.
The LOVELINUS that are here today,
and the LOVELINUS who were here yesterday.
We will greatly appreciate it if you cheer for LOVELYZ
so loud that the Olympic Hall would break down.
But before we continue, there's something you have to promise me.
The people at the standing area, please promise me
that you'll watch the concert safely.
Promise! Wah, thank you so much.
Then...
- Then?
- Shall we go to the next stage?
- YES!!
- Let's go?
Okey, let's go to the next stage. Let's go!!
♪ The lightly applied pink lipstick ♫
♪ My lies, my lies ♫
♪ This unfamiliar dress, will it look pretty? ♫
♪ It’s a style I put together ♫
♪ My lies, my lies ♫
♪ Don’t pretend not to notice ♫
♪ Slowly match your steps with mine like a song ♫
♪ I like that place far far away, with no one around ♫
♪ Let’s go far away so no one will notice us ♫
♪ Farther, farther, if it’s with you, just us two ♫
♪ The stars haven’t even come out yet, don’t rush ♫
♪ Just looking at my watch makes my heart pound ♫
♪ Oh yes, wait, the darkness will hide us ♫
♪ Then smile brightly, as much as we waited ♫
♪ Slowly match your steps with mine like a song ♫
♪ I like that place far far away, with no one around ♫
♪ Let’s go far away so no one will notice us ♫
♪ Farther, farther, if it’s with you, just us two ♫
♪ It’s not great but I packed our lunch ♫
♪ My lies, my lies ♫
♪ The last train is leaving ♫
♪ Let’s go to a strange place ♫
♪ My lies, my lies ♫
♪ Let’s forget everything ♫
♪ Kissing, kissing you baby is like the wind singing ♫
♪ Let’s dance together as if time has stopped ♫
♪ If you take my heart while having me in your arms ♫
♪ I won’t know what to do ♫
♪ Slowly match your steps with mine like a song ♫
♪ I like that place far far away, with no one around ♫
♪ Let’s go far away so no one will notice us ♫
♪ Farther, farther, if it’s with you, just us two ♫
♪ When did it become so natural? ♫
♪ We came to resemble each other ♫
♪ Even now as we’re walking together ♫
♪ Everything seems like a dream, I don’t want to awake ♫
♪ Slowly match your steps with mine like a song ♫
♪ I like that place far far away, with no one around ♫
♪ Let’s go far away so no one will notice us ♫
♪ Farther, farther, if it’s with you, just us two ♫
♪ Secretly, secretly ♫
♪ Will you come play? ♫
♪ When the clock turns twelve, it all starts to wake up ♫
♪ My memories, one by one, in the places  that lights reveal ♫
♪ When I start to really miss you ♫
♪ I see you beckoning me from far away ♫
♪ I know it’s a lie ♫
♪ But still, I miss you ♫
♪ Even if it’s a fantasy that I made up ♫
♪ Secretly, secretly ♫
♪ Alone, secretly ♫
♪ Will you come play? ♫
♪ Just for one more day, let’s pretend there’s no goodbye ♫
♪ Flutter, flutter ♫
♪ My heart flutters ♫
♪ If I close my eyes, like a miracle ♫
♪ You are by my side ♫
♪ The world starts to twinkle ♫
♪ The ferris wheel turned all night ♫
♪ The cotton candy was the sweetest in all the world ♫
♪ I remember the happy memories ♫
♪ You and I spun round and round ♫
♪ The ferris wheel turned all night ♫
♪ The cotton candy was the sweetest in all the world ♫
♪ I remember the happy memories ♫
♪ One more time, one more time ♫
♪ I don’t want to wake up yet ♫
♪ Let me stay a little longer ♫
♪ I want to sleep after I played all I can ♫
♪ Secretly, secretly ♫
♪ Alone, secretly ♫
♪ Will you come play? ♫
♪ Just for one more day, let’s pretend there’s no goodbye ♫
♪ Flutter, flutter ♫
♪ My heart flutters ♫
♪ If I close my eyes, like a miracle ♫
♪ You are by my side ♫
♪ It twinkles ♫
♪ Secretly, secretly ♫
♪ Alone, secretly ♫
♪ Will you come play? ♫
♪ Flutter, flutter ♫
♪ My heart still flutters ♫
♪ You’re so precious to me ♫
♪ Like a child, I can’t let go of anything ♫
♪ My love ♫
♪ The ferris wheel turned all night ♫
♪ The cotton candy was the sweetest in all the world ♫
♪ I remember the happy memories ♫
♪ You and I spun round and round ♫
♪ The ferris wheel turned all night ♫
♪ The cotton candy was the sweetest in all the world ♫
♪ I remember the happy memories ♫
♪ One more time, one more time ♫
The heat~
Wow, it was awesome today!
Everyone, this place is really...
The ferris wheel turned all night
This part was much louder than yesterday.
Since this is our JiAe's part...
shall we do it once more with JiAe's dance moves?
It's ok?
You should do it together with us.
Do it with us.
One, two, three, four...
♪ The ferris wheel turned all night ♫
♪ The cotton candy was the sweetest in all the world ♫
The reactions are so much better than yesterday.
The voice of our LOVELINUS is louder than the drums.
You are the best!
Joyland stage can only be seen during our concerts,
So it feels new to me.
You come to our concerts to do this, don't you?
You come here to sing the ferris wheel!
The ones at the back shouted together, right?
Right?
- Your voice is small!!
- One more!!
- Wow, they are the best.
- Thank you so much.
When we see up from here,
we can see people who don't answer to us.
- Who?
- Who is it?
I'll find you and go next to you.
- I'm going!
Who is it?
Push and pull!
JiSoo really wants to see you closer.
LOVELYZ wants to see you closer.
There's a stage we will go closer to you,
so see you closer later!
See you later~
For this concert being held in a long time,
we were at the training room just a week ago.
- Right?
- Yes, yes.
It was really fun but exhausting.
It was fun but tiring, yes.
We missed you all so much
that we wished time would fly.
After 'Now, We',
we worked so hard for this concert
thinking about our LOVELINUS.
- Let's each say what we actually did!
- What we actually did...
We went to Canada.
- Yes, we went to Canada.
- It's true.
To film 'LOVELYZ loves Canada'.
So we went to Canada and prepared our re-package album.
Soul learned yoga.
Let's stop talking about yoga.
We've been to Japan too.
- So it is.
- Yes.
We needed to charge ourselves after 'Now, We',
So we did take some time but it wasn't long.
With 'ALWAYZ' as the starting point,
we'll do our best in the second half.
- If we run.
- You run too.
- We should run together.
- LOVELINUS should.
Run!
Yes, LOVELINUS should run with us.
There's no time to rest, everyone.
Will you raise up your energy in today's concert too?
YES!!!
We will show our LOVELINUS the next stage~
Let's go!
Go!
♪ Knock, knock, hello? ♫
♪ Is anyone there? ♫
♪ Hello, hello, hello ♫
♪ Knock, knock, hello? ♫
♪ Is anyone there? ♫
♪ Knock, knock, it's me ♫
♪ Can you hear me? ♫
♪ Knock, knock, today I have something to say ♫
♪ Hold on, sit for a moment ♫
♪ Let me tell you my story ♫
♪ What I'm about to tell you,
may be hard to understand ♫
♪ Because even I don't know what was what ♫
♪ But if I keep hurting like this by myself,
I might get really sick ♫
♪ What do you think? Do I seem strange? ♫
♪ I like you so much, really like you ♫
♪ But why do I have resentment? ♫
♪ I’m anxious in case you find out ♫
♪ But why do I want you to find out? ♫
♪ What’s the reason that I pretend I don’t like you when I do? ♫
♪ What’s the reason I get upset when you don’t figure it out? ♫
♪ The weather is sunny ♫
♪ But it’s raining in my heart ♫
♪ The weather is cloudy ♫
♪ But suddenly, my heart is sunny ♫
♪ I’m not usually like this ♫
♪ But these days, I keep getting self-conscious ♫
♪ Even the littlest things make me go back and forth and dizzy ♫
♪ My countless emotions create a whirlwind inside ♫
♪ What do you think? Does it seem serious? ♫
♪ I like you so much, really like you ♫
♪ But why do I have resentment? ♫
♪ I’m anxious in case you find out ♫
♪ But why do I want you to find out? ♫
♪ What’s the reason that I pretend I don’t like you when I do? ♫
♪ What’s the reason I get upset when you don’t figure it out? ♫
♪ The weather is sunny ♫
♪ But it’s raining in my heart ♫
♪ The weather is cloudy ♫
♪ But suddenly, my heart is sunny ♫
♪ I hate that person for being so slow ♫
♪ Oh my but still, I like him ♫
♪ I’m talking about him but he still doesn’t know ♫
♪ What do I do with my love? ♫
♪ I like you so much, really like you ♫
♪ But why do I have resentment? ♫
♪ I’m anxious in case you find out ♫
♪ But why do I want you to find out? ♫
♪ What’s the reason that I pretend I don’t like you when I do? ♫
♪ What’s the reason I get upset when you don’t figure it out? ♫
♪ The weather is sunny ♫
♪ But it’s raining in my heart ♫
♪ The weather is cloudy ♫
♪ But suddenly, my heart is sunny ♫
♪ Knock knock, hello? ♫
♪Is anyone there? ♫
♪ Knock knock, it's me ♫
♪ Can you hear me? ♫
♪ Knock Knock, today ♫
♪ I have something to say ♫
♪ Hold on, sit down for a moment ♫
♪ There’s still a lot I haven’t told you ♫
♪ We’re still awkward with each other ♫
♪ I can’t look at your eyes because I’m too embarrassed ♫
♪ Today’s our first date ♫
♪ My heart is pounding, I like it so much but I’m nervous ♫
♪ How long will it be till you hold my hand? ♫
♪Should I link my arm with yours first? ♫
♪ Should I shyly lean on you first? ♫
♪ I’m too nervous, I’m too nervous ♫
♪ If we are together, oh baby ♫
♪ I become too nervous, my face is blushing ♫
♪ I wanna be your love♫
♪ Sweet and sour, I like it, sweet and sour ♫
♪ When I look at you my heart melts, I like you so much ♫
♪ You my love, you’re so perfect ♫
♪ You my love, you’re so great ♫
♪ Now you’re mine, don’t you dare look at anyone else ♫
♪ Sweet and sour, I like it, sweet and sour ♫
♪ Just like now, will you always love me warmly? ♫
♪ You my love, I was so surprised ♫
♪ You my love, I’m telling you I’m embarrassed ♫
♪ On the lips, on my lips ♫
♪ If you secretly kiss me, what will I do? ♫
♪ Anywhere is fine, as long as you’re with me ♫
♪ Even just walking will be nice If you hold my hand ♫
♪ Today’s our first date ♫
♪ We’re dating now, come to me like a man ♫
♪ How long will it be till you hold my hand? ♫
♪ Should I link my arm with yours first? ♫
♪ Should I shyly lean on you first? ♫
♪ I’m too nervous, I’m too nervous ♫
♪ If we’re together, oh baby ♫
♪ I become too nervous, my face is blushing ♫
♪ I wanna be your love ♫
♪ Sweet and sour, I like it, sweet and sour ♫
♪ When I look at you my heart melts, I like you so much ♫
♪ You my love, you’re so perfect ♫
♪ You my love, you’re so great ♫
♪ Now you’re mine, don’t you dare look at anyone else ♫
♪ Sweet and sour, I like it, sweet and sour ♫
♪ Just like now, will you always love me warmly? ♫
♪ You my love, I was so surprised ♫
♪ You my love, I’m telling you, I’m embarrassed ♫
♪ On the lips, on my lips ♫
♪ If you secretly kiss me, what will I do? ♫
♪ My two eyes widen ♫
♪ My two cheeks redden ♫
♪ The electricity tingles, it's like I've been shocked ♫
♪ I'm so nervous, I'm so nervous ♫
♪ You're my first one ♫
♪ The bells are ringing during my first kiss ♫
♪ Sweet and sour, I like it, sweet and sour ♫
♪ When I look at you my heart melts, I like you so much ♫
♪ You my love, you’re so perfect ♫
♪ You my love, you’re so great ♫
♪ Now you’re mine, don’t you dare look at anyone else ♫
♪ Sweet and sour, I like it, sweet and sour ♫
♪ Just like now, will you always love me warmly? ♫
♪ You my love, I was so surprised ♫
♪ You my love, I’m telling you, I’m embarrassed ♫
♪ On the lips, on my lips ♫
♪ If you secretly kiss me, what will I do? ♫
It's hot.
It's good to see LOVELINUS on the thrust, right?
Awesome!
It was so good.
We have many stages left to come closer after this, right?
Yes, we do.
So those at the thrust can have high expectations.
Everyone, how was the stage of 'Knock Knock'?
Was it good?
Just as I expected.
I searched on the Internet,
and I discovered that you were expecting a lot
about the 'Knock Knock' stage, am I right?
Did you see the loveliness of LOVELYZ?
Then we succeeded, thank you so much.
Will the loveliness that Kei talked about be shown on every stage?
Of course! I'm confident.
Then will you promise something to our LOVELINUS?
A promise!
I will go close to the area who shouts the loudest
and show them my aegyo.
Everyone~
Where should I go?
- Where should I go?
- Everyone.
Everyone, everyone, call us please~
It's too loud.
- Everyone.
- I choose here!
¡Kim JiYeon! ¡Kim JiYeon!
- ¿Have you decided?
- I decided.
- She decided.
- Show you aegyo.
Well, actually I...
After careful consideration,
I'll stay here.
I will show my aegyo to the people standing here.
There'll be another chances.
¡Lee MiJoo! ¡Lee MiJoo!
- Everyone!
- There will be more chances.
- I will show my aegyo!
- Everyone...
You shouldn't be like that.
Jiyeonnie is trying to do something.
So, I will show you my aegyo.
Will you count one, two, three for me?
Please, count one, two, three.
One, two, three!
Kei, show them too.
Show them too, please.
I was so embarrassed.
Thank you so much.
Please shout out loud.
Another member could go this time.
¡Lee SuJeong! ¡Lee SuJeong!
No, everyone. Not now.
Everyone, I won't.
Then, everyone...
Please keep quiet.
The shouting is so good at every stage,
how about seeing the aegyo of the members that you want?
Good~
You must be all ready.
They are curious about what the members were up to recently.
Suddenly emceeing?
- Sudden emceeing.
- I'll tell you what I've been up to.
I gathered a lot of excitement for today's concert.
I going to use all this excitement today so don't get tired first.
Promise me!
- Good!
- Promise me!
You are too quiet, do you like it?
- Very good.
But LOVELINUS doesn't get tired easily.
We know, it's true.
LOVELYZ has many refreshing and lively songs,
- but there also many good ballads.
- That's right.
We can't leave out our ballad songs.
Everyone, what ballad song do you want to listen?
'First Snow'.
- 'Shooting Star'.
Do you think you can listen to all these songs?
YES!!!
Then we prepared a song.
This song is JiSoo's favorite ballad song.
So we are going to sing it for you.
Then shall we start?
Everyone, please, listen carefully.
Go!
MiJoo, fighting!
♪ No, no, don’t end things like this ♫
♪ For me, for me I’m still curious about a lot ♫
♪ Our love is like an unfinished novel ♫
♪ But you’re trying to close the covers ♫
♪ I know, I know, I’m so stupid ♫
♪ Yes, yes, I’m all alone ♫
♪ So some day, you can open the cover and see me again ♫
♪ In between hope and anxiety ♫
♪ Wait, here I am in the frozen time ♫
♪ Look here I stand, so you can easily find me ♫
♪ Come back, here I stay so it’s not too late ♫
♪ Remember, I’m always here ♫
♪ I’m always in the same place ♫
♪ Holding tight to the meaning of you as I live again today ♫
♪ I hope the empty spaces will be filled ♫
♪ All my parts that haven’t been filled,
I hope they get filled with you ♫
♪ After carefully folding our memories ♫
♪ That were written deeply, word by word ♫
♪ I turn back and shed tears ♫
♪ Drawing you out in my heart once again, everything to me ♫
♪ No, no, even if it’s sad ♫
♪ Tears, tears, I won’t shed them ♫
♪ There’s still so much left to our story ♫
♪ It can’t be smudged by tears ♫
♪ Do you know, do you know? We were so happy ♫
♪ I don’t know, I don’t know, why did you leave me? ♫
♪ I’m praying again today ♫
♪ I’m still right here ♫
♪ In between laughter and tears ♫
♪ Wait, here I am in the frozen time ♫
♪ Look, here I stand so you can easily find me ♫
♪ Come back, here I stay ♫
♪ So it’s not too late ♫
♪ Remember, I’m always here ♫
[12th of July, 2017 at Woollim Building!]
[Misterious girls(?) enter the training room...]
[Why are LOVELYZ surprised??]
Hi?
LOVELYZ Diary 4.5.
You can only watch it at 'ALWAYZ' Concert.
Isn't it 4.5?
[It's not 4 and not 5, it's 4.5]
Wow, the are we filming LOVELYZ Diary?
We didn't know it too...
I asume we're going to places we went when we were filming LOVELYZ Diary.
I think HangGang river!
If we go to where we had out MT before, it'll be awesome.
- Wow~
- It's good, it's good.
We will ride public transport together this time.
[No, that`s not a good idea~]
(great) We can eat ice cream.
(sync) We can eat ddeokbokki~!
[Dance electronic dance...]
Are we going to do that?
The fear-some recognition test!
(100% honest) I hope we don't do that.
I hope we don't do that.
[What will LOVELYZ have to do???]
PD, what are we going to do today?
LOVELYZ Diary special shown at 'ALWAYZ'!!!
Shall we shout it out together???
We are very excited to film season 4.5 trough the 'ALWAYZ' concert.
This reminds me of our old times.
We'll do our best~ Fighting!
It feels like 5 instead of 4.5~
We hope the fans will enjoy the memories of the past 2 and half years.
What are we going to do today??
I don't know??
(suddenly) You now you are so pretty now, don't you?
[Members embarrased by the PD words]
-Yeah, what's wrong?
Of Course!
[Do you remember how pretty LOVELYZ member looked before??]
[LOVELYZ Diary Season 1 attacks!]
I've been a trainee for 4 years.
Yoo JiAe!!!
Don't look!!!!!
Why are you showing this???
I'm in trouble.
Everyone is so powerful.
[Caos because of the sudden attack of their past...]
We still have 3 hours left.
Hey, you had lots of hair back then.
[Wait, this song is??]
Do people know the song you sang?
[Kei is so embarrassed]
Almost 3 or 4 years?
[JIN can't even lift up her face...]
I think we have to work for the team.
[They are knocked down by the sincerity they had back on their debut]
I cut my bangs again in a year and a half.
[How SuJeong look like back then!!]
(envious) Yah~ You were so cute.
We practiced until the morning for a week.
SuJeong, you don't look chubby??
[She's happy...]
I't my first time going on a MT with the members.
[YeIn looks specially younger!!!]
You look the same.
So pretty.
[The are jeering to the maknae who wasn't honest]
[Anyway, they all look young and shy!!!]
So cute, so cute.
(again) LOVELYZ look so pretty now.
Pretty, pretty.
We look pretty back then too.
That's why he said that to us?
We didn't have any conscience.
[What's the most embarrassing moment of LOVELYZ Diary selected by the girls??]
Mr. PD worked on the subtitles and he did and evil job...
That I killed Solomon's seal tea...
[SuJeong killed Solomon's seal tea...]
(bold) I want to erase all season 1.
Our depressing moments?
My rap...
(punchline) Age means everything.
(destroys context) Why? Because I'm a mantis.
I almost broke the TV...
When we were on a test on season 1~
[She looks like the most depressed person in the world...]
For real, when we had to dance electronic dances.
The company wanted me to look chic.
Ah, I don't think so!
There are a lot of them?
The blind date part...
[But you said you liked it the most...]
I want to erase it.
[LOVELYZ is back with their training uniforms just like in the season 1]
[But they look so beautiful even with these clothes...]
Shall we practice while thinking of our past?
(cool leader) Let's see how this works out.
[LOVELYZ in singing acapella live in such a long time!]
[It sounds quite good instead the period of two years of blank??!]
(we can talk now) We don't have any parts!
No! Someone did tutututu!
[(never mind) No! Romance! No! Romance!!]
[It's a pity that we can't show the full version of the acapella]
(proud) It's fun.
It's fun since we are still good.
[Their acapella gets a pass!!!]
[What about their dance???]
[SongS they practiced while they were trainees, PLAY!!!]
[They looked good at first]
[But things start going wrong!!!]
What is next??
What??
[They aren`t sure but their bodies remember some of them]
[Kei who was doing good fails!!]
[JIN Who wasn't doing good fails!!]
(irritated) I can't remember!!!!
Keep trying!!
Film those three!
[We can't show the full version but it's a different pity from the acapella...]
You still remember quite much.
We are still young!
(sensitive) Sorry!!
I'm not that young!
(sensitive) You keep dissing ages these days.
(reverse) But I'm still young.
We looked back on our LOVELYZ Diary season 1.
We can't be boring like that!!
But we are funny nowadays~!
Shall we check in part 2??
[Even their comments aren't funny...]
[Anyway, Part 1 of LOVELYZ Diary 4.5 ends here!!!]
[Part 2 is Coming Soon after the stages]
♪ You’re my little lover ♫
♪ You’re my cute and little lover ♫
♪ Take me somewhere underneath the moonlight ♫
♪ Hold my hands and dance with me ♫
♪ You’re my little lover ♫
♪ You’re my cute and little lover ♫
♪ Take me somewhere underneath the moonlight ♫
♪ Hold my hands and dance with me ♫
♪ You’re my little lover ♫
♪ You’re my cute and little lover ♫
♪ With a moonlight like this, I don’t care where we go ♫
♪ Let’s dance all night, cheek to cheek ♫
♪ You’re my little lover ♫
♪ You’re my cute and little lover ♫
♪ I’m your little lover ♫
♪ I’m your cute and little lover ♫
♪ Take me somewhere underneath the moonlight ♫
♪ Hold my hands and dance with me ♫
♪ You're my little lover ♫
♪ I’m your little lover ♫
♪ You’re my cute and little lover ♫
♪ On a sleepless night ♫
♪ I’m sitting by the window ♫
♪ Looking at the sky ♫
♪ The blue scent of the night touches ♫
♪ My cold cheeks ♫
♪ In the middle of the night sky ♫
♪ Every time, a white morning star rises ♫
♪ Like my heart that waits for me ♫
♪ So I put it in my hands ♫
♪ This is my spot ♫
♪ I won’t change at all ♫
♪ Like that star that stays every day in the same place ♫
♪ In case you forget me ♫
♪ I’m shining the brightest ♫
♪ A white star that is always looking at you ♫
♪ When morning comes ♫
♪ Though it’s hidden for a moment ♫
♪ It’s never gotten farther ♫
♪ Just like my heart in the beginning ♫
♪ This is my spot ♫
♪ I won’t change at all ♫
♪ Like that star that stays every day in the same place ♫
♪ In case you forget me ♫
♪ I’m trying to shine brighter ♫
♪ Don’t forget... ♫
♪ That I’m always here ♫
♪ A farewell ♫
♪ The dark sadness has fallen ♫
♪ I’m shining more as I wait ♫
♪ This is your spot ♫
♪ Put your head up and look ♫
♪ A white star that is looking at you, again today ♫
♪ Not a relationship that’s just about holding hands without any feeling ♫
♪ I want a more electric you ♫
♪ More aggressively, more closely, come ♫
♪ Baby, baby, c'mon ♫
♪ Dinner, coffee, movie, not that typical stuff ♫
♪ But you know that heart-racing, secret thing ♫
♪ Don’t you know what I want? ♫
♪ Hey! I want The... ♫
♪ The thing that’ll make my heart dripping wet ♫
♪ The thing that makes me tremble just thinking about it ♫
♪ Why are you so slow, do I have to say it? ♫
♪ I want more ♫
♪ Don’t just tickle me ♫
♪ Be a man and fight for me till the end ♫
♪ The time is now boy, take me ♫
♪ Baby kiss on my lips ♫
Let's go!
Scream!
♪ Not being able to sleep just at the touch of our hands ♫
♪ That girl is gone, there are fireworks in our eyes ♫
♪ Why don’t you know what I’m talking about? ♫
♪ Hey! I want The... ♫
♪ The thing that’ll make my heart dripping wet ♫
♪ The thing that makes me tremble just thinking about it ♫
♪ Why are you so slow, do I have to say it? ♫
♪ I want more ♫
♪ Don’t just tickle me ♫
♪ Be a man and fight for me till the end ♫
♪ The time is now boy, take me ♫
♪ Baby, kiss on my lips ♫
♪ Is it because you’re nervous? ♫
♪ Is that why you can’t even think about it? ♫
♪ Look at me ♫
♪ My eyes that have you in them, I'm telling you ♫
♪ The thing that’ll sweetly melt my heart ♫
♪ The personal and secretive thing ♫
♪ Do I need to explain even more? ♫
♪ I want more ♫
♪ I don’t need you to save me up ♫
♪ What you wanna do right now? ♫
♪ That’s it boy, come here ♫
♪ What’re you looking at? ♫
♪ Appreciate, are you gonna just keep looking? ♫
♪ Don’t just tickle me ♫
♪ Be a man and fight for me till the end ♫
♪ The time is now boy, take me ♫
♪ Baby kiss on my lips ♫
Let's go!
Everyone, are you going to end up like this?
Shall we do it once more?
Shout it out!
♪ Hey! I want The... ♫
♪ The thing that’ll make my heart dripping wet ♫
♪ The thing that makes me tremble just thinking about it ♫
♪ Why are you so slow, do I have to say it? ♫
♪ I want more ♫
♪ Don’t just tickle me ♫
♪ Be a man and fight for me till the end ♫
♪ The time is now boy, take me ♫
♪ Baby kiss on my lips ♫
[LOVELYZ has gathered in front of Woollim Building]
Everyone! Did you like our stages?
Shout it~ if you liked it!
[She seems to have emceed for a concert before...]
They were happy, they were happy~
So~ LOVELYZ Diary 4.5 is back!!
[What's on part 2 of LOVELYZ Diary 4.5???]
[Taking photos at the memorable places of LOVELYZ Diary!!!]
Baby Soul, Kei and me
(deviation episode) went to HanGang tiver.
It feel so good.
I want to go on a blind date!
I want to go to Gapyeong again!
Gapyeong!
I want to try the recognition test.
What about doing the avatar blind date again...
What I want to do the most is going on a blind date...
I also want to play games in teams.
[Anyway!!! Let's go to that memorable places, go!!!!]
(blind date) I want to do it again.
[Revealing their honest thoughts as soon as it starts]
- I think it will be different is we do it now.
It would be fun.
[The cafe were LOVELYZ had their blind date]
[There are pictures on the cafe wall]
- Oh, look, my autograph it's here!
Where's yours?
- It's here.
- Oh, it's here.
You didn't know this was me.
- I was looking for your short hair.
- I didn't remembered too.
There were lots of changes.
[How will they feel if they sit down where they had their blind date?]
[Awkward x 1000000]
It feels like I'm on a real blind date.
I know!
If we do it again, It could become a good memory.
Um... again...
[They were talking for 30 minutes about the blind date...]
(In conclusion) It was really fun.
Hey, isn't this cheesecake delicious?
(takes the bait) Should we take it?
Oh? I brought my lock&lock!
[Classless lock&lock ad-lib...]
Wow, I don't think that's a good idea...
Wait! You told us to take it!
(anyway) We enjoyed the cake.
At least we reminisced old memories.
[Baby Soul and Kei succeed in reminiscing memories!!!]
[Now it's JiAe and MiJoo's team!!! (BGM: Not Better than Strangers)]
Everyone, think. We are best. Think about how we became partners.
Baby Soul and Kei are best friends too.
They both should have worn handcuffs (ft. Lovelyz in Wonderland).
[JiAe and MiJoo's memory is! Deviation episode!!!]
We'll take sticker photos.
Since we are pretty, let's do something simple.
It doesn't matter what we do...
[Hard to deny...]
That's right.
[Punch game comes after sticker photo!!!]
[MiJoo's pose looks very natural!!!]
You're good, aren't you?
(but I'm better...)
[Her identity was forgotten for a while...]
- This is delicious.
- Yes.
[They are both enjoying free time, using deviation as an excuse.]
- It's fun.
MiJoo and JiAe~
Let's go.
[Special edition of MiJoo and JiAe's deviation succeeds!!!]
Are you guys enjoying this time?
[What is YeIn looking on the cellphone??]
It's here, it's here, I've found it.
[The legendary hot dog GIF at the HanGang river]
The legendary photo.
We are thankful to LOVELINUS for loving these moments of us.
[Good-mannered]
Thank you so much.
[LOVELYZ are always excited whenever they come to the HanGang river]
Everyone, look at the view!!
We are at Hangang river!
[JiSoo and YeIn did a good mission with the bear costume]
Do you know who we are?
[JiSoo is the origin of the lying back show]
Hello, everyone. I'm back.
Lying down show, JiSoo!!
[They keep doing dance moves that are awful to watch!]
[Sit down for the hot dogs]
- You are all happy, right?
- LOVELINUS, we'll be alwayz by your side.
That's why we are here today.
[What legendary GIF will they create today...]
The hot dog GIF file af 2017.
At HanGang river~ YEINDOG! (means: YeIn puppy).
Ah! I'm doomed! Ah! I'm doomed!
[Try it again since you are already doomed!]
You're cute, you're cute.
[JiSoo also succeeds at make the same facial expression]
[JiSoo and YeIn's team, succeed at reminiscing the memories of the hot dogs!!!]
We did a recognition test at Hongdae.
True, true.
And by chance, you and I did it in the same place.
I know, it's amazing.
[How will the awareness of LOVELYZ be in 2017...]
[JIN and SuJeong get off feeling worried!!!]
We're here!!!!
[They arrive at the same spot]
It was here, it was here, it was here.
[People are gathering right after they arrive!!]
They aren't coming to us, but I think they recognize us.
Let's take some pictures.
[People keep greeting LOVELYZ endlessly!!!]
Hello, she's running away!!
Hello!
[The heat is getting higher!!!]
- Hello!! WoW!!!!
No one knew us before.
And we feel so honored to have a morale boost time.
Right before our concert.
[Someone who looks to be a SuJeong fan arrives!!!]
I love you, SuJeong!
[A lucky LOVELINUS!!!]
- LOVELYZ are the best!
[JIN and SuJeong had the chance to meet people happily!!]
Since we knew your nickname, he must be a LOVELINUS.
[All the four teams succeed at reminiscing memories!!]
[LOVELYZ gathered at the rooftop of the company to end season 4.5]
It felt good because it reminded us of the old times.
But we are in the middle of a concert now.
It's a really unique video.
- LOVELYZ Diary season 4.5 will be only played at 'ALWAYZ'.
- Only at 'ALWAYZ'.
And nowhere else!
Where are we? Only at...!
[LOVELYZ Diary season 4.5 limited at 'ALWAYZ']
Only at 'ALWAYZ'! Limited for two days!!
Please, have fun with the rest of the stages.
-Have fun with the stages!
- The stages will be something unique!
And also really fun!
What stages are left?
[Inducing intuitions of 'ALWAYZ']
What you can only see at 'ALWAYZ'.
Aren't you curious?
Yes!!
[Then shall we go back to 'ALWAYZ' stages?]
This has been LOVELYZ Diary season 4.5.
♪ What do I do? What do I do? ♫
♪ Since I was young, in case someone else comes to me ♫
♪ And steals my heart, I hid it safe and sound ♫
♪ My hair that falls to my shoulders is shiny ♫
♪ This S line is for you ♫
♪ My make-up is so natural ♫
♪ All I need is for you to come ♫
♪ Now, time to attack! ♫
♪ I’ve truly fallen in love ♫
♪ I hear the sound of my heart in my head ♫
♪ Only for you, I am determined ♫
♪ I even bought heels to wear♫
♪ You like me too anyway ♫
♪ So will you be a man and confess to me? ♫
♪ Actually, this is my first time in love ♫
♪ I’m not lying ♫
♪ Love is aya aya aya ♫
♪ Head, shoulders, knees and toes, knees and toes ♫
♪ My knees go aya aya aya ♫
♪ Head, shoulders, wearing heels ♫
♪ The one and only diary that protects my secrets ♫
♪ What kind of love will it be? ♫
♪ Will it be like the destiny of love at first sight? ♫
♪ What will you call me? ♫
♪ Oh my, will you call me honey? ♫
♪ I’m laughing so much ♫
♪ My mom thinks it’s just a phase ♫
♪ Now, time to charge! ♫
♪ I’ve truly fallen in love ♫
♪ I hear the sound of my heart in my head ♫
♪ Only for you, I am determined ♫
♪ I even bought heels to wear ♫
♪ You like me too anyway ♫
♪ So will you be a man and confess to me? ♫
♪ Actually, this is my first time in love ♫
♪ I’m not lying ♫
♪ I don’t expect a lot ♫
♪ I just want one thing, to be honest
(One thing I promise) ♫
♪ My shy heart has something to say to you ♫
♪ I like you!! ♫
♪ Hurry and tell me it too ♫
♪ Each minute and second is precious in my love story ♫
♪ Have you seen a movie without a female star? ♫
♪ Oppa! ♫
♪ An action movie without romance? ♫
♪ Oppa! Oppa! ♫
♪ The Best Actor award, how do they receive it? ♫
♪ Love is aya aya aya ♫
♪ My knees go aya aya aya ♫
♪ Whenever I see you eyes, I get so nervous ♫
♪ Without knowing, I’m hiding from you ♫
♪ Awkward arms ♫
♪ Awkward lines ♫
♪ Will I ever become the star of the show? ♫
♪ Take 1, Take 2 ♫
♪ Only NGs keep increasing ♫
♪ Take 4 and Take 5 ♫
♪ When will I start being natural? ♫
♪ Scene number one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight ♫
♪ It’s been a while ♫
♪ When will you recognize me? ♫
♪ I feel like the ending will come like this ♫
♪ I feel so anxious ♫
♪ Do you know my name? ♫
♪ I’m a cameo ♫
♪ Whenever I see the shining you, it hurts so much ♫
♪ I could be good too ♫
♪ But my desire to be good gets ahead of me ♫
♪ One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight ♫
♪ Only NGs keep increasing ♫
♪ You probably didn’t know ♫
♪ But there were a lot of scenes where we passed each other ♫
♪ Short greetings ♫
♪ Short conversations ♫
♪ Can’t I be your co-star? ♫
♪ Take 1, Take 2 ♫
♪ Only NGs keep increasing ♫
♪ Take 4 and Take 5 ♫
♪ When will I start being natural? ♫
♪ Scene number one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight ♫
♪ It’s been a while ♫
♪ When will you recognize me? ♫
♪ I feel like the ending will come like this ♫
♪ I feel so anxious ♫
♪ Do you know my name? ♫
♪ I’m a cameo ♫
♪ Whenever I see the shining you, it hurts so much ♫
♪ I could be good too ♫
♪ But my desire to be good gets ahead of me ♫
♪ One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight ♫
♪ Only NGs keep increasing ♫
♪ Even though I’m timid ♫
♪ I want to receive your spotlight ♫
♪ Next episode, next episode ♫
♪ I see the end, what do I do? ♫
♪ When will I start being natural? ♫
♪ Scene number one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight ♫
♪ It’s been a while ♫
♪ When will you recognize me? ♫
♪ I feel like the ending will come like this ♫
♪ I feel so anxious ♫
♪ Do you know my name? ♫
♪ I’m a cameo ♫
♪ Whenever I see the shining you, it hurts so much ♫
♪ I could be good too ♫
♪ But my desire to be good gets ahead of me ♫
♪ One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight ♫
♪ Only NGs keep increasing ♫
The reactions are so hot.
It feels like we might burn, it's hot.
Your reactions are so hot.
Everyone, we came up to the closer stage.
Can people far away also see us?
Can you?
We will go closer~
This is the 2nd floor, and this is the 3rd floor.
- It's very vague.
- 1, 2...
I don't know where is the 3rd floor.
The 2nd and 3rd floor joins here.
- 2.5
- I see.
Ah, 1.5 floor.
You join together because LOVELINUS is one, right?
Please, everyone, give me some good reactions.
Please, give me good reactions.
- Did you watch LOVELYZ Diary 4.5?
- Yes!!
How was it?
Do you want season 5?
- Do you want it?
- Yes!!
Then we should film it, don't we?
- We should film it.
- PD JinSoo, where are you?
We showed a unit during 'LOVELYZ in Winterland', remember?
And today it was a different unit.
- Did you enjoy it?
- YES!!!
- But I... what?
- Thank you so much.
- He said 'Morning Star' is the best.
- Wow, thank you.
'My little lover' is the best. 'The' is the best.
They are saying we are all the best.
All the stages were so good, but I personally think...
JiAe and JiSoo's 'My litte lover' was very impressive.
What was the intro?
I purposely... who came to 'LOVELYZ in Winterland'?
Me!!!
Wow, a lot of you came!
I wanted to remind you of the memories, and continue the feelings,
So I used a music box for the intro, which was our song 'Doll'.
What do you think?
- It was so good. Unnie, I really liked it.
- Thank you so much.
It's like a fantasy.
And JiAe played the piano by herself.
JiAe really practiced hard playing the piano.
It turned all night.
- It turned all night?
- The piano sound went on all night.
She's the best.
We were thinking about what to do.
I learned the piano when I was young.
I prepared it in such a long time just for you.
How was it?
- It was really good.
- Thank you so much.
Yoozart, Yoozart!
How was 'Morning Star' from our team?
It was so good!
Everyone, you're the best.
We will try to come up with more ballad songs.
I cried at the backstage room listening to 'Morning Star'.
- Really?
- Yes.
But your make-up looks neat.
My make-up?
I cried inside.
When I was fixing my make-up at the waiting room,
I saw the 'Morning Star' on the sky.
Yes, thank you.
Even the LOVELYZ members had high expectations on the 'Morning Star' stage.
Give them an applause.
Then shout out as much as you liked the high school rock performance.
That YeIn, MiJoo and me did together.
The reactions are really hot today.
Our...
Wow, yes, thank you so much.
What to do?
Did you get wet from the water gun of our love?
But my water gun didn't work again.
Me too. I was trying to shot, but it didn't work.
Ah, really? I shot a lot today.
Like this. This is what I did.
I'm upset, I wanted to shoot all of you.
We did that because we were worried that LOVELINUS might feel hot today.
Was it cool? Okay then, next time it'll be iced water.
We'll shoot it for you.
- Next time we should use large bowls.
- Large bowls?
- Large bowls.
- Will it be okay?
Ah, yes, well.
We prepared three unit stages for 'ALWAYZ' this time.
Are you curious about how our next concert will be?
I'm also curious about how the combinations will be.
I heard Incheon Fam, Incheon fam.
- Incheon fam?
- Incheon fan!
Incheon fam, yeah!
- I'm two-SuJeong.
- Two-SuJeong! Two-SuJeong!
We are JinJi, JinJi.
Okcheon, Okcheon!
Okcheon!
JinJi, JinJi!
Mi-JiAe, Mi-JiAe.
You girls, are used to be roommates before.
The manager thought we weren't close enough, so she set us up.
- And even wore cuffs.
- Now we are very close.
You are close now.
Yes, we are closer than anyone.
That's right.
- Yes?
- They want to see.
Kiss! Kiss!
- It's embarrassing.
- You don't know wich units will perform in concerts ahead us.
You have to come to our concerts.
You should be!
It's a promise.
How was the 'Aya' stage that you've been waiting for
after the 'Knock Knock' stage?
Was it good?
Good, good.
- We were cute.
- Were we cute?
I think the stethoscope choreography was the point.
Point.
We also threw t-shirts.
JiSoo and I threw them.
And we shoot with guns, right?
Who got the T-shirts?
Who got them? Put your hands up.
-Lucky guy, it went far.
- It really did.
It went really far.
Where are you?
- It went really, really far.
- Where is he?
- It must be the only one who can't see.
- I can't see too.
- To be honest...
- Congratulations!
When I was shooting the gun, one bullet went out,
so I threw the T-shirt to this side.
So one from here got it, and another one from there.
- Angel.
- So wistful.
- It's nice that you got it in different areas.
- yes, good!
YeInnie hurted her leg during Cameo.
Perfect whole LOVELYZ.
Finally you can see the version with the eight of us.
YeIn, how do you feel?
I feel so good now since it feels like I'm in album promotion activities with you. I'm happy.
I was so happy that I could finally perform 'Cameo' in front of more LOVELINUS.
I liked it too.
If you like it, then
What?
If you liked it, then let's go to next stage.
Alright, alright.
- The next stage is...
- What are we going to sing next?
What are we going to sing now?
The two song we are going to sing now
are LOVELYZ's emotional ballad songs.
- Let's go.
- Let's sing them now.
♪ We are moving in a circle ♫
♪ Really perfect circle ♫
♪ This circle around with unshrinking radius ♫
♪ And I draw another circle ♫
♪ Inside of it, I draw to more circles ♫
♪ At last i draw a pretty heart shaped lips of yours ♫
♪ Then i draw a little speech bubble ♫
♪ And I write my name there ♫
♪ I imagine what you're going to say to me and write it there ♫
♪ Someone might see this ♫
♪ So I erase it and turn to the next page ♫
♪ But you, who I drew is looking at me ♫
♪ My movement is always the same ♫
♪ A circle that has you inside ♫
♪ Draw, draw, draw ♫
♪ And just like a white moon there ♫
♪ I'm moving in a circle ♫
♪ A star that can never see you ♫
♪ Draw, draw, draw ♫
♪ I just circle around you ♫
♪ I should've told you, ♫
♪ It'll get harder tomorrow ♫
♪ Just like a problem that I couldn't solve because I put off ♫
♪ I should have smiled when our eyes met ♫
♪ In your eyes, I would have been just a cold girl ♫
♪ But you are actually a bit bad ♫
♪ You can pretend to be happier ♫
♪ In that moment when you look at me ♫
♪ But you always do as much as I do ♫
♪ No, you do less than me about minus one ♫
♪ So you make me feel like it's not enough ♫
♪ My movement is always the same ♫
♪ A circle that has you inside ♫
♪ Draw, draw, draw ♫
♪ And just like a white moon there ♫
♪ I'm moving in a circle ♫
♪ A star that can never see you ♫
♪ Draw, draw, draw ♫
♪ I just circle around you ♫
♪ What I always draw is your face that looking at me ♫
♪ Draw, erase, draw ♫
♪ You're always there ♫
♪ We're moving in a circle ♫
♪ Just like the hands of a clock ♫
♪ To the left, to the left, to the left ♫
♪ Where are we now? ♫
♪ The wind that blows is drawing ♫
♪ The sweet but cold scent of yours ♫
♪ Even though I close my eyes and try to resist ♫
♪ It sinks down my mind with you ♫
♪ I lie down on the hill listening to the grass's whisper ♫
♪ And I feel bitter but warm about you ♫
♪ I pray as I hold my hand tight ♫
♪ For the future that I can hold your hands over the distant cloud ♫
♪ Secret heaven ♫
♪ Like a flower that lost its scent ♫
♪ Like a spring that lost its flowers ♫
♪ I feel like I lost my light ♫
♪ Like a child who is lost ♫
♪ I lost everything ♫
♪ Wandering, looking for you ♫
♪ Whether it’s night or day ♫
♪ In my memories ♫
♪ My head ♫
♪ You’re covered ♫
♪ In this dark night ♫
♪ I’m wandering through ♫
♪ Then I collapse as I'm trapped in here ♫
♪ In my empty heart ♫
♪ In my empty night ♫
♪ You come find me entering more and more ♫
♪ I can’t escape ♫
♪ In my night, in my empty heart ♫
♪ Give yourself back to me ♫
♪ Give myself back to me ♫
♪ My meaningless ♫
♪ Day, day, day, day, night and ♫
♪ Day, day, day, day, night and day ♫
♪Day, day, day, day, night and day ♫
♪ The sun rises and sets ♫
♪ Night comes and goes ♫
♪ Every minute, every second is the same ♫
♪ Floating around the deep night ♫
♪ I’m an endlessly falling star ♫
♪ Everything is getting forgotten ♫
♪ Whether it’s night or day ♫
♪ In my memories ♫
♪ My head ♫
♪ You’re covered ♫
♪ This dark night, I’m wandering through ♫
♪ Then I collapse as I'm trapped in here ♫
♪ In my empty heart ♫
♪ In my empty night ♫
♪ You come find me entering more and more ♫
♪ I can’t escape ♫
♪ In my night, in my empty heart ♫
♪ Give yourself back to me ♫
♪ Give myself back to me ♫
♪ My meaningless ♫
♪ Day, day, day, day, night and ♫
♪ Day, day, day, day, night and day ♫
♪ To others, the sun is bright ♫
♪ But for me, it’s just nighttime with light ♫
♪ Times I thought I was going forward ♫
♪ It was just me walking in the same place ♫
♪ You come find me entering more and more ♫
♪ Give yourself back to me ♫
♪ Give myself back to me ♫
♪ My meaningless ♫
♪ Day, day, day, day, night and ♫
♪ Day, day, day, day, night and day ♫
♪ The wind softly blows ♫
♪ And comes through the open window ♫
♪ Shaking up my memories ♫
♪ Now I know why I couldn’t sleep for all this time ♫
♪ I thought it would hurt more ♫
♪ I thought I would hate you more ♫
♪ But I feel more at rest, now I know why ♫
♪ I was upset ♫
♪ As much as I was too young ♫
♪ I said I liked you ♫
♪ But only thought of myself ♫
♪ At our inexperienced break-up ♫
♪ My heart got ahead of me ♫
♪ That’s why I got hurt ♫
♪ Now I wanna tell you ♫
♪ Love is emotion ♫
♪ In a corner of the times that I’ve had ♫
♪ I’m so glad you were there ♫
♪ Goodbye~ ♫
♪ The only moonlight ♫
♪ My eyes hurt, tears rise up ♫
♪ A smile slowly spreads ♫
♪ In the spilling memories, you are there ♫
♪ If only I knew your heart more ♫
♪ If only we looked into each other’s eyes ♫
♪ Would we have come farther?
Now we’ll never know ♫
♪ I was upset ♫
♪ As much as I was too young ♫
♪ I said I liked you ♫
♪ But only thought of myself ♫
♪ At our inexperienced break-up ♫
♪ My heart got ahead of me ♫
♪ That’s why I got hurt ♫
♪ Now I wanna tell you ♫
♪ Love is emotion ♫
♪ In a corner of the times that I’ve had ♫
♪ I’m so glad you were there ♫
♪ Tossing and turning, I wake up at once ♫
♪ Countless nights I couldn’t fall back asleep ♫
♪ I’m drawing you out on the corner of the past ♫
♪ Memories of you fill my heart ♫
♪ Now I’m trying to erase and empty it out ♫
♪ I was upset, as much as I believed in you ♫
♪ I took you for granted ♫
♪ I didn’t think of you ♫
♪ Now I wanna tell you ♫
♪ Love is emotion ♫
♪ In a corner of the times that I’ve had ♫
♪ I’m so glad you were there ♫
♪ Goodbye~ ♫
There are new stages at this concert, right?
Yes~
That is why you must come to LOVELYZ concert.
-Yep, that's true.
-That's true.
Because LOVELYZ concerts show everything we can.
It's full of charming points.
- LOVELYZ is giving everyhting like the giving tree.
- Fascinating LOVELYZ concert.
There are too many stages that lots of you already saw.
So there's more chances for you to have fun with LOVELYZ.
But you look a bit tired, MiJoo.
Everyone! Are you tired?
No!!!
If you are tired, MiJoo will get to you. What did I say?
Are you tired?
No!!!
- Shall we test it by screaming?
- How can we check that?
- How are you going to check them?
- Then first of all...
Let's divide you by sections and do the shouting test.
Good, good.
Let's divide into standing area, and seats.
Four of us for each section.
- Four on this side. And others on that side.
- Four, four!
- Then, we take the standing area?
- We'll take the seats then.
Kei's side will take the seats.
Are you confident? We will show aegyo
to those who shout out softer.
Shouldn't we show aegyo to those who shout louder?
You are right. Are you ready for the aegyo? Soul unnie?
Yes, we are going to show our aegyo
to the area with louder voices.
The aegyo set... If our team wins,
What about Baby Soul's one-shot aegyo time?
If your team wins?
- If your team wins.
- If we win.
Isn't it if we lose?
Yes, if we lose.
And automatically that team will win.
- Yes, if we win.
- We are being so stupid now.
We keep changing words.
- If our team wins.
- Our team.
Who is in your team?
We are the seat section.
They take the seat section,
and we take the standing section.
And if the voices of the seat section are louder,
our team has to do aegyo.
That's right, that's right.
We will show aegyo to the area with louder voices.
Yes, right.
Are you ready? Clear your throats.
Wow, so good.
They practiced, they did.
- It's so fun.
- They are so good.
They are good.
They are good. They are better than me.
Shall we practice ourselves?
- Yes.
- Shall we?
- We are...
- Shall we step forward?
Let's go closer to the seat section.
I'll tell you how to do it this time.
If we shout 'LOVELYZ' you guys can shout back 'I love you'.
- I love you!
- Okay?
Seat section, fighting!
- Let's go, seats.
- Pull out your energy, everyone.
Practice, practice.
Shall we practice warming up?
Shall we?
Since the members are already out there,
let's warm up the seats first.
One... go!
One, two.
- If we say 'seats' then they say 'I love you LOVELYZ'.
- We... no, no, no.
If we shout 'LOVELYZ'.
LOVELINUS should shout out 'I love you'.
LOVELYZ.
I LOVE YOU!!
Will the standing section practice too?
- We can't lose.
- Do we start too?
Stop, until here when they practice.
Until here when they practice.
Now, one, two, three.
LOVELYZ.
I LOVE YOU!!!
- Is it just how I feel? I think we are more...
- We can't lose, the seating area can't lose.
We can't lose.
- This is the real game now, everyone.
- This is real.
It's real now.
Everyone, please, show us what you have.
Show what you have.
One, two, three.
LOVELYZ.
I LOVE YOU!!!!
- Good, good.
- Thank you.
- The standing area, we can't lose.
- Shall we run to the front?
- Shall we run?
- We will go to the seats.
Then MiJoo and I will try to receive some responses here.
Then Baby Soul and I will do it here.
- Please, shout it loud.
- Hello~
Can you hear it?
- One... let's go.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- MiJoo, we'll start.
- Go on.
Two, three.
LOVELYZ.
I LOVE YOU!!!!!!!
The voice at the seating is louder.
You are the best. You rule.
- We won.
- Good job.
They sounded similar.
But LOVELINUS are one.
- It's hard to choose the winner.
- How can we compare them?
Everyone, how could we compare the
shouting of our LOVELINUS?
Shall we go back to the main stage?
- Lee SuJeong! Lee SuJeong! Lee SuJeong! Lee SuJeong!
- Why me?
They want to see Baby Soul's aegyo.
Both the seating and standing area were loud enough.
- All the areas...
-Yes, they both were.
So let's shout out...
'LOVELINUS, we love you' all together.
We will.
Lee SuJeong! Lee SuJeong! Lee SuJeong!
They want Soul's aegyo.
Yesterday, each of us showed our charms
through LOVELYZ Diary.
But since a lot of LOVELINUS want Baby Soul's aegyo,
she can go last.
Okay, she can adorn the finale.
We should say 'LOVELINUS, I love you',
and it will start from JiSoo there.
Since the message must be delivered
without being stopped,
we will say 'LOVELINUS, I love you' endlessly.
But Baby Soul will do it longer.
Happy?
- Starting from this side, right?
- Yes, from that side.
You know the first runner
gets the most nervous.
- This has to go on without any pause.
- You can do it.
You can do it, JiSoo.
Everyone, we won't have any pause between.
We should do it fast.
It will end in two shakes.
- It'll be fast!
- You must cheer for us.
On the count of one, two.
One, two, three.
LO.
We are starting right now, right?
- Yes, don't talk.
- Do it right way.
- We must do it now.
- Again, again, again.
There shouldn't be embarrassing pause.
If you do it like that, we must start over.
Let's do it in a relay then.
I'll dot it, I'll dot it, I'll dot it.
In a relay.
- Fighting, JiSoo.
- Start from 'LO' again.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
LO.
Wait, wait, I can't do it because the fans are screaming.
- They can't hear my voice then.
- Everyone, everyone.
It's so funny.
Then, let's do it like this.
- Scream after it's over.
- Yes, after it's over.
Please, put back your voices for the moment.
You get to scream after Baby Soul finishes it.
Take in your breath, and scream after 'YOU'.
Yes, yes. That is so.
Let's do it again. It won't end this time.
- Most of them are looking at jiSoo now.
- Hey, I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Good~
I like it.
G~o.
I'll start!
G~o!
Isn't it LOVELINUS?
It's NUS.
It's LOVELINUS.
What did you say?
Ah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I'm stupid.
Empty brains.
- Kei, Kei.
- It's 'LOVELINUS I love you'.
- You did it in purpose, right?
- To do it again.
I thought it was 'LOVELYZ, I love you'.
- One more time.
- Let's start again.
Let's go, from the beginning.
If this goes on, showing aegyo
becomes something easy.
But you now what?
It's a pain for those who are waiting.
I know, what should we do?
What to do?
What about me?
- JiSoo will be in most pain.
- I'm so sorry.
This will be the last for real, go.
LO.
VE.
LI.
NUS.
S.
I.
LOVE.
YOU.
What was that?
We'll sing our next song since we are embarrassed.
I think we are ready.
Are you ready to run?
It's an exciting stage.
- Let's run.
- Let's go!
♪ Did you had a long day? ♫
♪ I see a bit of sadness ♫
♪ Let today pass and tomorrow come ♫
♪ I’ll make you happy ♫
♪ The times I’ve wanted to cry ♫
♪ I knew you’d come and hug me ♫
♪ Now, I’ll be the one holding your hand ♫
♪ Look at me and smile ♫
♪ Keep your head up, I’ll be there for you ♫
♪ My beloved ♫
♪ When things get tough you can lean on me ♫
♪ Let’s share our dreams ♫
♪ All this great love I have for you ♫
♪ My beloved ♫
♪ Are you having a busy day? ♫
♪ Don’t skip any meals ♫
♪ Let today pass and tomorrow come ♫
♪ Think happy thoughts ♫
♪ In times flying by so quickly ♫
♪ We feel like we can’t get enough ♫
♪ Now, I’ll be the one holding your hand ♫
♪ Look at me and smile ♫
♪ Keep your head up, I’ll be there for you ♫
♪ My beloved ♫
♪ When things get tough you can lean on me ♫
♪ Let’s share our dreams ♫
♪ All this great love I have for you ♫
♪ My beloved ♫
♪ Even if we can’t be together as time goes ♫
♪ Don’t be sad ♫
♪ You’re the only one for me ♫
♪ Keep your head up ♫
♪ You’re are my one and only, most beloved ♫
♪ When things get tough you can lean on me ♫
♪ Let’s share our dreams ♫
♪ All this great love I have for you ♫
♪ My beloved~ ♫
♪ Don’t open it yet ♫
♪ Even if you’re curious ♫
♪ Don’t drop it either ♫
♪ Then I might shatter ♫
♪ Here’s my heart ♫
♪ Be even more careful ♫
♪ Because it’s as delicate as glass  ♫
♪ Don’t leave me alone often ♫
♪ Because I get lonely ♫
♪ Don’t lose me either ♫
♪ Then I might disappear ♫
♪ Don’t feel assured so easily ♫
♪ My heart might change... ♫
♪ like the weather ♫
♪ Can I give it to you? ♫
♪ Will it be okay? ♫
♪ Will you be surprised? ♫
♪ My heart ♫
♪ And your heart ♫
♪ I wish it was the same ♫
♪ I’ve folded up my confessions ♫
♪ I’m still inexperienced with love ♫
♪ So I’ll carefully place it all here ♫
♪ And send it to you ♫
♪ To you ♫
♪ Stop coming to me ♫
♪ Let’s keep it as it is ♫
♪ Don’t stare at me ♫
♪ Then I can’t lift up my head ♫
♪ Let’s walk a bit more, just like this ♫
♪ I know, I have a lot of thoughts ♫
♪ Will it be ok...? ♫
♪ To give you my all? ♫
♪ Will you preciously protect me? ♫
♪ My heart ♫
♪ And your heart ♫
♪ I wish it was the same ♫
♪ I’ve folded up my confessions ♫
♪ I’m still inexperienced with love ♫
♪ So I’ll carefully place it all here ♫
♪ And send it to you ♫
♪ The secrets are stacking up ♫
♪ My heart has never felt this way before ♫
♪ So I’ll carefully place it all here ♫
♪ And send it to you ♫
♪ I looked at you ♫
♪ Past the wall ♫
♪ On my tip toes until you disappeared ♫
♪ In that spot ♫
♪ I wrote your name ♫
♪ But now I wanna tell you ♫
♪ Accept my heart that has fallen in love ♫
♪ It’s racing again like this ♫
♪ I’ve folded up my confessions ♫
♪ And I’ll send it to you ♫
♪ The secrets are stacking up ♫
♪ My heart has never felt this way before ♫
♪ So I’ll carefully place it all here ♫
♪ And send it ♫
♪ To you ♫
The last!
Please, handle it with care.
- Enjoy them.
- It's our feelings for you.
Enjoy your ice cream.
Did you get it?
Well, let's have fun now.
Shall we have fun?
Let's start a fire~
What song is this?
- Are you all ready?
- Are you ready to jump?
Let's play!!
Jump, jump, jump.
Jump, jump, jump!
♪ Come a little closer ♫
♪ Just come 1cm closer ♫
♪ Can you feel my heart? ♫
♪ No, you don’t  ♫
♪ I easily get angry at you ♫
♪ Then it scares me, what if we grow apart? ♫
♪ I think it’ll become awkward ♫
♪ You fool~ ♫
♪ Just promise me one thing ♫
♪ 1cm closer ♫
♪ Slowly come into my heart ♫
♪ So my poor heart won’t get hurt ♫
♪ Come to me ♫
♪ I wanna hide my shy heart ♫
♪ And walk next to you ♫
♪ Though I still can’t say it ♫
♪ I’ll confess to you some day ♫
♪ I easily think of you ♫
♪ Then it scares me, what if you disappear? ♫
♪ I wanna see you for a long time ♫
♪ You fool~ ♫
♪ Just promise me one thing ♫
♪ 1cm closer ♫
♪ Slowly come into my heart ♫
♪ So my poor heart won’t get hurt ♫
♪ Come to me ♫
♪ I wanna hide my shy heart ♫
♪ And walk next to you ♫
♪ Though I still can’t say it ♫
♪ I’ll confess to you some day ♫
♪ Sometimes, I wonder if I should go to you first ♫
♪ But then my cheeks just turn red ♫
I LOVE YOU!!
♪ 1cm closer ♫
♪ Slowly come into my heart ♫
♪ So my poor heart won’t get hurt ♫
♪ Protect me~ ♫
♪ I wanna hide my shy heart ♫
♪ And walk next to you forever ♫
♪ Only look at me till the end ♫
♪ I’ll honestly confess to you ♫
[ Truth Talk ]
JiAe.
You keep wearing your hair in two ponytails
to look young, don't you?
(Rather) When I do, it's...
It looks like I'm pretending
to look young when I'm old...
I never did it to look young.
I heard that I look young with it.
LOVELYZ isn't funny at all without me.
Yes!! I agree!!
Am I wrong?
'Did you have your meal?'
You are saying this to make your vogue word, right?
Completely not!!
Oh my! Aren't you being too mean now?
I really love to ask after people who I like or are close to me.
'Did you have your meal?' Like this.
I didn't mean anything else.
You want to be the same age as me, right?
Nope? Because...
I like being young!
Social life made me realize something.
That I want to be young...
I want to be young! I'll be young!
When you are eating something and I ask you for a bite,
Sometimes you don't want to share.
This is what I want to ask YeIn.
When I ask her for a bit...
Her eyes look very uncomfortable.
We both don't want to share...
But we both ask for a bite.
You want to be the youngest member, right?
Sometimes I want to be the youngest~
But I want to be the eldest more.
Seri! Ous! Ly!
I'm not pretending to be nice... I'm serious!!!
I just want to be a big sister to the younger members.
I wonder why you always look for YeIn first...
More than the other members!
Other members make me feel comfortable too,
But YeIn makes me... very calm.
And she makes people comfortable when they are around her.
[Then what did Baby Soul ask to YeIn?]
It's hard to say by myself.
What did you eat to be so pretty?
Is that a question?
Ah~ Hold on~~
I think Baby Soul thinks I look pretty~
Because I am the youngest member.
She's pretty. I wonder what she eats.
What did I say to JiAe?
What hurts you the most now?
Calling me Yoo JiAe.
She doesn't call others by their full names.
But she calls me...
Yoo! JiAe...
Why did you become a flower?
You know the reason~
You can see that I'm a flower.
I'm sorry.
I have a big smile.
Should I say my face blooms? Just like a flower blooms.
They say I smile like that.
And everyone agreed to it.
No one will know who Kei is if I'm with a flower~
Who is Kei?
Which two members will you take
if you have to go to a deserted island?
Wow~ This is a killing question!
I will take YeIn and JIN.
The others...
Are old now so I'll let them rest~
Do you like cup noodles the most among all food?
Because I always eat cup noodles?
There are lots of food if I widen my world!
What I can think of is only cup noodles~
Yukgaejang The Love!
You actually enjoy people making you show aegyo, right?
Ah! No... Never~~ No.
It's not nice to disappoint people so I just do it.
I really hope that no one asks me to do aegyo!
I don't avoid it these days.
Do aegyo!
No!!
Was I avoiding it?
Is your future dream still a fruit store?
To be honest, it's changing a bit~
I'm now twenty two and I think realistically...
It might disappoint our fans.
But it's getting a bit far from the fruit store.
Soemtimes you pretend not to know
when you know you are pretty.
Ah... but~
I am trying so hard...
To think that I'm pretty.
But I don't think I am really that pretty.
I don't know~
I'm the best at this among LOVELYZ!
My collarbone is pretty!
I'm in charge of collarbones.
I can fill water in my collarbones.
I am a collarbone beauty.
No~ I have the best collarbones~~~
The eight girls talked honestly for the first time!
I'm pissed off!
This is how they get closer with each other once again~~!
JiAe pisses off really often.
I really didn't know.
Why is she asking me that when she's not much different?
[ Truth Talk ]
♪ You’re my destiny ♫
♪ I can’t look away ♫
♪ You’re all I see ♫
♪ You’re my destiny ♫
♪ I can never leave you ♫
♪ You’re my Earth ♫
♪ The center of my day ♫
♪ Why do you keep circling around her? ♫
♪ When I revolve around you like the moon ♫
♪ I can’t take a step closer to you ♫
♪ You know how this feels too ♫
♪ Do you dream of her tonight? ♫
♪ Even when I shine on you ♫
♪ You end your day that way ♫
♪ But for me, a day feels like a month ♫
♪ I hope the dream stops ♫
♪ I hope the night wakes ♫
♪ I hope waves come crash with your calm heart ♫
♪ You’re my destiny ♫
♪ The gravity that pulls me ♫
♪ I can’t look away ♫
♪ You’re all I see ♫
♪ You’re my destiny ♫
♪ I can never leave you ♫
♪ You’re my Earth ♫
♪ The center of my day ♫
♪ Your heart keeps leaning ♫
♪ Hot or cold it grows with the seasons ♫
♪ But my heart that is always directed to you ♫
♪ Not a single breeze of wind to be felt ♫
♪ Oh, how your day glows ♫
♪ Is there no room for me? ♫
♪ My heart fills then tips over ♫
♪ For me, a day feels like a month ♫
♪ I hope the dream stops ♫
♪ I hope the night wakes ♫
♪ I hope waves come crash with your calm heart ♫
♪ You’re my destiny ♫
♪ The gravity that pulls me ♫
♪ I can’t look away ♫
♪ You’re all I see ♫
♪ You’re my destiny ♫
♪ I can never leave you ♫
♪ You’re my Earth ♫
♪ The center of my day ♫
♪ For once... ♫
♪ If I could stand between you and her ♫
♪ To hand you the ring of light ♫
♪ For once, just once, if I could block her from you ♫
♪ And fly through your day ♫
♪ You’re my destiny ♫
♪The gravity that pulls me ♫
♪ I can’t look away ♫
♪ You’re all I see ♫
♪ You’re my destiny ♫
♪ I can never leave you ♫
♪ You’re my Earth, the center of my day ♫
LOVELINUS, you are the best at shouting!
The best!
The best, the best!
You are feeling hot too, right?
Aren't you? The best.
Those who are feeling hot, please, cool down
with the ice cream you got before.
It's our gift for you.
Who got ice cream? Who did?
I threw as hard as I could so that
they would reach the seats.
- But it didn't reach far.
- I threw it like this.
I also practiced very hard.
To send it until the end, but it didn't make it.
Did anyone at the seats receive one?
I threw it to the seats.
- There it is.
- He got it.
- Did someone get mine?
- I think we threw about half.
Well, if you see that ice cream,
there are Poloraids pictures on it.
- Poloraid?
- Polaroid.
- She's having a hard time these days.
- There are polaroid pictures on it.
And for today, there are also blank photos too.
- Who got the blank photos today?
- Yes, there are blank photos.
Please, look forward to it.
As a new surprise,
we gave you selfies during '1cm'
and I hope you take good care of it.
Everyone, how did you find the Truh Talk with LOVELYZ?
Did you like it?
We asked funny questions in order to
make LOVELINUS laugh. Right, YeIn?
I didn't mean a single thing that I asked.
That sounds like a total lie.
Whenever you offered me food,
you always made me want to eat it so much!
It's true, it's true.
One bite is always the most delicious part.
One bite of ramen is the best.
Ramen is delicious.
You like ramen.
- Cup noodles are so good.
- MiJoo likes cup noodles.
- She really dos.
- Yes, she does.
Everyone knows.
Yukgaejang, Yukgaejang!
Didn't you eat it today?
I ate it today morning.
- And you ate it yesterday too.
- It's good, I ate it yesterday too.
You should film an advertisement.
I wasn't on the video,
if there's something I'd like to ask, I want to ask JIN.
What is it?
I am so curious about what you dream when you sleep.
Do you know why, everyone?
Our JIN talks in her sleep and it's so spectacle.
I am the witness, everyone.
So I really want to know what
she dreams in her sleep.
Me?
I usually don't dream.
But recently, I just...
Dreamed of someone I saw on that day.
JiSoo and I share the same room.
And you said that you heard something.
She really talks a lot in her sleep.
And it sounds like as if she is uttering a spell.
She talks cutely in her sleep.
It's cute, nothing special.
Yes, she's a baby.
- Baby JIN.
- A 22 years old baby?
- LOVELINUS are my friends.
- Yes, it is.
The next stage will be our new song.
The tittle of the song is 'Fallin''.
And the lyrics are what we want to say to LOVELINUS.
Please listen carefully.
♪ You, you, you, you, you ♫
♪ I’m Fallin’ in your eyes, listen ♫
♪ An unknown warmth, yeah ♫
♪ Comes and fills me up ♫
♪ Your voice and even your face ♫
♪ Even your child-like eyes ♫
♪ Slowly, are we resembling each other? ♫
♪ If I’m alone, I get lonely ♫
♪ Farther away, lonely ♫
♪ This sweet dreaming ♫
♪ I wanna look at you all day ♫
♪ Into each other’s eyes, fallin’ ♫
♪ All moments of the day, I’m fallin’ ♫
♪ When our hands touch, will you call my name? ♫
♪ So I can prettily draw you out? ♫
♪ Even if the colors all fade, I’m fallin’ ♫
♪ I hope you’re my last, yeah ♫
♪ I hope my prayers will be answered ♫
♪ Small scars, even tears ♫
♪ Even fights we may have ♫
♪ Everything stops, they will all pass ♫
♪ If I’m alone, I get lonely ♫
♪ Farther away, lonely ♫
♪ This sweet dreaming ♫
♪ I wanna look at you all day ♫
♪ Into each other’s eyes, fallin’ ♫
♪ All moments of the day, I’m fallin’ ♫
♪ When our hands touch, will you call my name? ♫
♪ So I can prettily draw you out? ♫
♪ Even if the colors all fade, I’m fallin’ ♫
♪ I wanna be like the first time every day ♫
♪ Even if we get comfortable and numb ♫
♪ Let’s keep the feeling of our first love ♫
♪ If it's you, I’m confident ♫
♪ Without change, until always ♫
♪ Into each other’s eyes, fallin’ ♫
♪ All moments of the day, I’m fallin’ ♫
♪ When our hands touch, will you call my name? ♫
♪ So I can prettily draw you out? ♫
♪ Even if the colors all fade ♫
♪ I’ll Be There, always by your side ♫
♪ I’m Fallin’ ♫
How was our song?
Did you feel our heart?
Yes!!!
- Thank you.
- Falling in LOVELYZ.
You speak good english.
They said 'Falling in LOVELYZ'.
Did you see the lyrics on the screen while we were singing?
Yes.
We wrote every letter ourselves.
Fallin' which we sang for the first time in this concert,
was given from composer Marco who
worked with us for the first time.
It's a song that expressed a farewell beautifully.
Just like LOVELYZ and LOVELINUS are in love?
- Ah, I'm so shy.
- Yes, right.
The song released today is our new song.
But it might be included in our new album,
so please look forward to it.
Well, everyone.
LOVELYZ and LOVELINUS
always think about eachother.
But still, time flies so fast.
That's true.
What should we do?
- That's right.
- Why?
What should we do?
It's because the concert is going to end up soon.
We have 3 songs left.
Really?
I don't want to go.
Nope!
Shall we hold an all-night concert
next time just like SuJeong said?
Yes!!!
Will it be fine?
It's such a pity, but if there's farewell,
there's also a next meeting.
Shall we thank some people
before we say goodbye?
Shall we?
I'll go first.
Our Woollim family!
Executive producer Lee JoongYeop, chairman
Honseok and including the management family.
I am really thankful.
JiYoung, our choreography instructor.
Who spent nights with us for every new song.
JiYoung, who stay up all night with us.
And also thank you to our
hair stylists and make-up artists
Who made us look beautiful.
And also to the stylist staffs...
And Interpark, production music,
sound, light and video directors, thank you.
And thank you to Mr. Jin Soo PD
who filmed the LOVELYZ Diary 4.5 VCR.
And thank you so much to INFINITE's SungGyu
and SungYeol who came to watch our concert.
Thank you.
The best! Sunbaenims, you're the best!
And there are people who made summer
concert 'ALWAYZ' shine more.
We will introduce you our LOVELYZ band
who made live performances possible.
Song-Gi for base.
Don't play the same thing as yesterday.
Ah, he's so cool.
- He's cool.
- Thank you.
And next.
DongYoon for drum.
Scream, scream.
And SeongBum, the pink guitar man.
What are you doing?
- And MoonHee for keyboard!
- Cool.
MoonHee~
♪ Do you remember me? ♫
♪ I was happy, next to you ♫
♪ It was a white night ♫
♪ Remember me ♫
♪ Don’t forget me ♫
Seong-Kyeong, the band master,
who makes our songs more plentiful and exciting.
Finale.
I thought the song started.
And YeongRok, the protool engineer,
who is doing his best at the console.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
And there's more.
The ones we thank the most.
Who do you think it is?
Who?
- Who?
- What?
Yes, it's you, LOVELINUS.