We truly thank you for being with us today
on Weekly Idol.
- Thank you.
We'll do our best today.
- Whether it's here...
- Or there...
In the end... Weekly Idol!
The Thumbs Up Idol of the Week
have amazing credentials.
They've done 260 concerts.
They're amazing rookies.
Thumbs Up Idol of the Week. IN2IT!
They're flying in.
They look great.
Is this "Gee?"
Goodness.
("Gee" 2x version)
(Can they express the sentiment
of girls in love?)
(Let's go, IN2IT)
(IN2IT is making me tremble)
(Cute / Adorable)
(They're so dreamy)
(IN2IT is making me tremble)
(So much for getting any sleep tonight...)
(Let's do the killer part)
(It's like it's IN2IT's song)
(So cute)
(This is perfection)
They're going right into the next one.
This is their new song.
"SnapShot."
("SnapShot" 2x version)
(They suddenly get manly...)
(Thank you so much... Sigh)
(Why does this look a bit silly?)
(So amazing)
(Make everyone possessed)
(Time for some fast dancing)
(Taking snapshots)
(They have to keep moving
their upper bodies)
(We're falling for them, they're so good)
(We have to remember something so amazing)
(Be responsible for my heart beat)
(Power walking)
IN2IT!
Amazing.
Thumbs Up Idol of the Week! IN2IT!
You guys were amazing.
Catch your breath first
and greet the people.
We'll greet everyone.
Come on! Hello, we're IN2IT!
Please be good to us!
Thumbs Up Idol of the Week. IN2IT.
"SnapShot."
You keep taking photos
during the dance.
And you pose like models too.
The song sounds great even at 2x.
Thank you.
I was so impressed.
They're supposed to get 3 seconds to talk
about song but I'll give them 5 seconds.
(Unexpected good news)
We'll give you 5 seconds to
tell us about "SnapShot."
Go ahead!
With Madonna's song "Vogue" from 1990
as the theme,
it's a song that makes you think of
models on the runway!
(He did it in 5 seconds!)
He even had time left.
(Such good pronunciation)
You know "Vogue" by Madonna?
Yes.
The dance goes like this.
Now it's time to move on.
Let's do the Charm Mining Cam.
Come on, Director Yoo.
Director Yoo's Charm Mining Cam.
Get some epic clips.
(Director Yoo's Charm Mining Cam)
As Director Yoo approaches you,
show off all your skills and talents.
In Ho.
This is what I prepared.
Jang Do Yeon's high fashion model pose.
I'll give it a shot.
Director Yoo, follow me.
Hurry and follow him.
(This should be an amazing clip)
One. Click.
(Nice detail)
Two. Click.
(Bending)
Three. Click.
Four...
(I'm In Ho of IN2IT)
This pose was funny.
Do Yeon, are you watching this?
You should do model poses with me one day.
(He even sent a message to Jang Do Yeon)
Nice.
Who are you going to next, Director Yoo?
- It's Director Yoo.
- In Pyo?
His lips are really dry! Isaac!
(When did he see that?)
Isaac! His lips look dried out.
I'll do a cover of Celeb Five's song.
(Really?)
- A cover.
- Really?
- A dance cover.
- A dance cover?
Okay. I'm dancing with you.
(Isaac is touched)
("Celeb Five" by Celeb Five)
(Looking great)
He's making the right face!
(So into it)
(Nobody can stop Isaac)
(This is more exciting than
the original version)
(So exciting)
(Isaac is so excited!)
He's into it.
(Going into 2x speed)
I knew this would happen.
(A tough dance)
(Hang in there, Isaac)
(Aaah)
(So funny)
(Chaotic dancing)
(Isaac showed off his skills)
(Huffing)
(Didn't expect 2x speed, did you?)
He looked so determined.
That was great.
2x! What was that?
This show isn't that easy.
Alright, we saw Isaac.
Next is In Pyo.
Hello, I'm the super sexy leader, In Pyo.
I'll show you all
a dance cover for Sun Mi's "Gashina."
(In Pyo will dance to "Gashina?")
(How will he pull this off?)
("Gashina" by Sun Mi)
(Sexy, flexible and on point)
Such pretty lines.
(His sexy moves look so precise)
He dances like J-black.
(He's supposed to be sexy and cute
but he's so dreamy)
Look into Director Yoo's camera.
Director Yoo, move up more.
(Director Yoo works hard to
make an epic clip)
Get closer, Director Yoo.
I don't want to.
I'll just move from here.
(This is already epic)
(Everyone cheers)
Go!
That's it!
(Shaking the camera)
(All over the place)
Here comes Director Yoo!
(Great job, In Pyo)
We saw the real Director Yoo.
I got a good shot there.
(I gave it my all...)
Director Yoo's Charm Mining Cam.
This has been the handsome
and talented group IN2IT.
You guys have any closing words?
We still have so much more
to show you all.
So I hope you all can support us.
Please try to look for us
and show us some love.
Please be good to us.
And we'll continue to try harder.
Please look out for us!
Thank you.
This has been IN2IT!
It's the Idol of the Week.
No need to introduce them.
Let's just bring them in.
You seem so happy.
It's been so long since
I've seen them.
What are you talking about?
These people...
Who are they?
You're so happy.
I feel different.
You feel different?
I feel embarrassed.
- Your ears are red.
- I don't know...
- Why?
- I don't know!
What's wrong with you both?
Bring them in now.
Idol of the Week!
Lovelyz!
Hello.
(They come in like a spring breeze!)
(Ye In)
(Ji Ae)
(Su Jeong)
(Mi Joo)
(Baby Soul)
(Ji Soo)
(The group that spreads love, Lovelyz)
Hello, we're Lovelyz.
You haven't been on our show in a year.
And when you were here last year
you had another year-long absence.
Is it Yearly Idol for you girls?
Yearly Idol...
Lovelyz came out with a new song.
Tell us about "That Day."
Who's going to talk?
- About the song.
- Mi Joo.
I've never seen a female idol do this.
"Tell us about your song."
They usually do this.
But Mi Joo went...
She called out to me with her chin.
(Earlier)
(How did she see that?)
You do it.
Who?
You do it!
So funny.
- I'll talk.
- JIN.
It's a therapeutic song.
What's our concept?
Clear and cool.
We're so refreshing in our music video.
You'll all fall for us.
Please listen to our song
when you're sick.
- When we're sick?
- It'll cure you.
Really?
Even our dance has some
moves that cure you.
- In the beginning...
- Right?
(Blow)
This makes you feel better?
It blows your pain away.
- Hoo, I'll cure you.
- Of all illnesses?
("That Day" by Lovelyz)
(Clear and cool)
(Lovelyz will cure all my scars)
(It's time to be cured by Lovelyz!)
(At the tip of my nose, hwa)
(In my mouth, hoo)
(The dance is so catchy)
They cure you.
(They're so sweet, chic and bubbly)
(Cold memories, hwa)
(Collect everything, hoo)
(My body feels cured from hardships)
(All cured)
(Clapping)
Lovelyz...
You guys were floating around
so lightly like feathers.
Lovelyz always sound so lovely.
Even people that don't know them
will want to
know them after hearing this song.
They have their own style.
Their unique style.
That style is important.
You girls are on our show after a year.
Did you know we came out
with a 2x dance?
I've seen a lot of over groups do that.
Do you want to try it?
I thought it would be fun if we tried that.
Will it be perfect?
I don't know about that
but it should be fun.
- As long as it's fun.
- That's the best thing.
The song at the original tempo
sounded therapeutic.
It has to be therapeutic at 2x speed
to be perfect.
It has to have that same feeling
which makes this hard.
Why does it smell like kimchi stew
now that Lovelyz is here?
Someone must've eaten.
It's for another segment.
Is that what it is?
We have to see "That Day."
"Hoo" but it smells like kimchi.
♪ Hoo, kimchi stew, hoo ♪
Shall we see Lovelyz do the 2x dance
to "That Day"?
Get in formation.
- This is our first time.
- It's our first time.
- It is?
- Yes.
- You never even practiced this?
- No.
Really?
We'll let you hear it first.
This is how fast 2x is.
Cue the music.
(Their minds go blank)
- Oh, no.
- This is too fast.
(They start dancing along)
That's very good.
Okay, that's all you get to hear.
I couldn't hear the beat.
While everyone else was shocked
I saw Ji Ae focus on the moves.
(Me?)
(So calm)
I guarantee that Ji Ae
won't make mistakes.
Really?
I make the most mistakes.
Ji Ae won't make mistakes.
She's the best dancer.
Lovelyz will do the 2x dance for
the first time. Cue the music!
Cue the music!
("That Day" 2x version)
(Hey! They're good at this!
They're a bunch of liars)
(So busy)
(How are you girls so precise?)
Don't step on me.
(Mi Joo's sensitivity comes out)
She stepped on her.
"Don't step on me."
She stepped on me.
(Wobble)
This is doable.
They said it's doable.
(They haven't made a single mistake so far)
(So bubbly)
(Hwa)
(Hoo)
(They really draw you in)
(Hwa)
(Hoo)
(It's the Lovelyz heart flower)
Is it the entire song?
(Huffing and puffing)
(She said it was doable but
seems the most tired)
(After almost falling,
Su Jeong looks on point)
I think it's the entire song.
(Kei dances at 2x too)
Hey, we're doing well.
(Impressed at themselves...)
(This is so hard)
(They really are doing well)
(Moving into formation)
My arms hurt.
(Tired... Except for Ye In)
(The song is almost over)
(A final burst of prettiness!)
(No, don't end!
We want to watch this forever)
Look at Ji Ae. No mistakes.
They ran into each other!
But they didn't make mistakes.
(Lovelyz succeed at the 2x dance)
- That was so fast.
- Their steps were so light there.
They were very light on their feet.
We'll give you time to drink some water.
They were good but they had a lot to say.
They kept talking.
"You stepped on me."
"That was you."
"We're doing well."
"We're doing a good job."
"Did you step on me?"
Don't step on me.
You stepped on me.
Hey, we're doing well.
Take it easy for now.
Baby Soul's dimples were
visible the entire time.
She kept that same face.
And Ye In is the youngest...
"Take it easy for now."
This group talks a lot.
They pulled off the 2x speed dance.
They did well so they should
do something else.
(What else?)
A new segment we prepared.
The Rollercoaster Dance.
You just did the 2x speed
dance for "That Day."
There's a rollercoaster version
that goes super slow, original tempo
and 2x speed.
It gets super fast and then super slow.
And you have to stay on beat.
(Shows a bad example)
Even your lips.
Right, even your lips. Lip-synch on beat.
They have a lot of great songs.
So for the first time today...
(What is it?)
- The Random Rollercoaster Dance.
- Really?
No!
That should be hard.
"That Day" and your hit song "Ah-Choo."
We'll combine those two songs
for a Rollercoaster Dance.
They get a big prize if they succeed.
For a cleaner dorm and
better teamwork...
We need that.
Sang Min got you a vacuum cleaner.
How many rooms do you have?
4 rooms.
Sang Min will get you 4 vacuum cleaners!
4.
(Sang Min's wallet is in
trouble every episode)
It's cordless? Wow.
It's cordless.
- You still use one with a cord?
- Yes.
You'll trip over that.
You'll hurt yourself.
(We can't have Lovelyz trip and fall)
The Random Rollercoaster Dance.
Please get ready.
I'm excited.
You can talk it out first.
(They'll do the dance move for
first verse's hook)
(Help each other if you don't know)
Let's tell each other.
(Act nonchalant if you make a mistake)
They talk the most amongst each other.
They talk a lot.
Mi Joo even has her back
to the cameras.
To focus. For real.
She's signaling with her chin again.
Okay.
I guarantee that Ji Ae
will make no mistakes again.
No mistakes from Ji Ae because...
When everyone else was
focused on the meeting
she wasn't paying attention...
(This is unrelated to me)
So...
I'm positive. I'm sure.
No mistakes from Ji Ae.
The Rollercoaster Dance!
Cue the music!
("That Day" Random Rollercoaster Version)
Like this?
(It's so fast!)
(The 3 hosts are focused)
(Ji Ae is already struggling?)
(Nope! She gets right on track)
Ji Ae, we let that slide.
(Ye In starts it off)
(So pretty)
(Nobody was surprised
when the tempo changed)
(Here come Baby Soul's dimples!)
(It slows down)
(In trouble)
The slow part.
Nice, Jin!
(Aaah!)
(No! Must stay focused!)
Mi Joo!
(It seemed so different)
(Mi Joo's hwa and hoo)
(Lovelyz is in bloom)
(Light on their feet)
(Is this the original tempo? They're so good!)
(Let's change the song)
("Ah-Choo" Random Rollercoaster Version)
Su Jeong came in acting.
But the song changed.
Mi Joo.
(Running after Su Jeong)
My body feels more heavy.
(Now they're ready for "Ah-Choo")
(Su Jeong in the center)
(Ye In the future chef)
(Kei is so adorable)
(Cute)
(Trips up)
(Acts like it never happened
and looks for the camera)
(Here comes the killer part)
(You don't know how I feel, ah-choo)
(Let's see this pretty
and slow part again)
(So pretty)
(Dancing well)
Her dimples won't go away.
(Cute)
(The beat gets faster)
(Save Ji Ae)
(Mi Joo and Su Jeong seem fine)
(The 8 girls combine)
(Pauses)
What was that?
Just go for it!
(These wily staff members...)
(You can't make your mistake so obvious...)
- This is making me sneeze!
- You're out!
I feel like sneezing.
You're out.
- This isn't right.
- Really?
We were right.
Ah-choo. It goes like that.
They had a brief meeting
before doing the move.
Ji Ae, do you go in like this?
Is this how you come in?
(Ji Ae seems confused here)
Is this part of the dance?
(Please believe me...)
(These two pretend it's the killer part)
Really?
Before you go into the hook
do you have a meeting first
and then start dancing?
We have a brief meeting. 1, 2, 3, "Ah-choo."
That's what you do?
They had a summit there.
(Lovelyz have a summit)
After your meeting and counting to 3,
Ji Ae came out like this.
That was my gesture.
She's the main dancer.
I go like this and walk out.
Jin must be honest.
She feels bad about lying.
Jin, what do you say?
It's true.
We don't have a move like this.
(The 3 hosts vs. Lovelyz)
It doesn't exist.
No head-scratching move?
Would you like another chance?
But one less vacuum cleaner.
3 in total.
That's fine.
You'll play rock, paper, scissors
for them.
We'll share them.
I'll remember this part, Ji Ae.
With 3 vacuum cleaners on the line.
Cue the music!
("That Day" Random Rollercoaster Version)
(Light on their feet despite the fast beat)
(Perfect formation)
(Here comes the youngest)
(And here comes Mi Joo)
(Aaah!)
(Acts casual)
(Heart attack)
(Time for the beat to get faster!)
(A fast wink)
(Cold memories, hwa)
(Collect everything, hoo)
Mi Joo's face!
(The 8 girls combine)
(They quickly find their places)
(So relaxed)
(They're used to this)
("Ah-Choo" Random Rollercoaster Version)
Line up!
(Mi Joo is here)
(They're like butterflies)
I feel so heavy.
(They're all in place)
(I want to eat Su Jeong's cooking)
(I'm a cooking newbie)
(Kei's hidden cuteness)
(A total mess...)
Baby Soul!
(Let's watch this great part in slow motion)
(About to sneeze)
(Light on their feet)
(I'm so ticklish, I can't take it)
(The beat gets fast!)
(She's peeking)
Ji Ae!
(I'm watching you!)
(Eyes on Ji Ae)
Ji Ae is so good.
(Hehe)
She does have this move.
(The 3 hosts are falling for these girls)
(Baby Soul, why is your back turned?)
Hold on, Baby Soul.
Baby Soul. Baby Soul.
Baby Soul.
She took a trip somewhere.
(The Lovelyz flowers)
(Almost done! Let's do this)
(Hang in there, girls)
(Like a row of flowers)
(Jin lets you know the song is almost over)
(The 8 butterflies get together)
(We look so pretty)
You guys succeed!
Amazing.
You get 3 vacuum cleaners for your dorm!
Congratulations.
This is great.
Jin was the most serious.
Aside from her mistake...
- From beginning to end...
- She just did her job.
She just went her way.
- She was staring at the floor.
- Right.
"What should I do after this?"
Time to analyze Lovelyz.
Lovelyz Self-Written Reports.
Show Yourself!
Let's look at these self-written reports.
Baby Soul.
Being a good daughter. Mom. Memo.
Comeback. Diet.
It's nice to see that she wants
to be a good daughter.
But memo is a lot bigger than mom.
Diet is bigger than being a good daughter.
- There's an order.
- Right.
Mom is near her mouth.
She keeps saying it. Mom.
"Mom! Where are my socks?"
"Mom, I told you to do this for me!"
(Baby Soul is a good daughter)
For skills she wrote...
Monster voice.
Monster voice. Right.
Can you go do it over there?
Over here?
Into our ears?
This might scare you.
(We have no idea what to expect)
Baby Soul has such a pretty voice.
Hold on. Why are you behind me?
I'm a coward. I'm a scaredy-cat.
It's a monster voice.
Hello there.
(Hello there)
(Laughs)
So scary!
(Cheerful)
How'd you do that?
I could make that voice since 1st grade.
In elementary school?
I don't know how I do it.
I can just make that voice.
You woke up one day
and sounded like that?
"I'm going to school now."
You have to block your throat
with your uvula.
Easier said than done.
How do you block your throat
with your uvula?
She's good.
I bet she can do the crying rap
with that voice tone.
Sang Min will demonstrate.
It's supposed to come from the stomach.
(I was excited about doing this for you)
(Watching the passionate crying rap)
She's going to do this?
Try to sound the same.
5, 6, 7, 8.
(I was excited about)
(LOL)
♪ I was excited about ♪
Does anyone here think
they can do it?
The crying rap?
I think Su Jeong would be good.
Okay. Ready?
(Gravelly!)
(Breathes in)
5, 6, 7, 8...
(I was excited about doing this for you)
- That was pretty good.
- Nice.
Ji Soo, you try now.
(I used all my money
to buy you a gift)
(Pleased)
Mi Joo.
- You want me to try?
- Go ahead.
(I was excited about you)
(She's good!)
(I was excited about doing this for you)
(Transforms)
- Time out.
- What's with those eyes?
Hold on.
We have to protect Mi Joo.
Your eyes...
♪ I was excited about ♪ That was like...
(Her face really sold the rapping)
Her eyes...
I liked that she had fun with it.
(Don't do that to your pretty face, Mi Joo)
- Ji Ae.
- Let's see Ji Ae.
For her skills she wrote...
"The monster voice
I learned from Baby Soul."
Why were you hiding it?
Why didn't you say something?
You wrote it down.
Let's have them talk to each other.
- With monster voices.
- The monster talk.
Since you were trainees...
Baby Soul.
What?
Baby Soul sounds scary.
Thanks for teaching me the monster voice.
You have to be louder.
(LOL)
That was...
(She's a good teacher)
(Growling)
(Can Shin Young do the monster voice?)
That was Lee Gye In.
(Baby Soul is pretty funny)
How'd you know?
Next member...
(That was funny)
Next is Ji Soo.
Her skill...
I want to focus on what she crossed out.
"DC."
Despicable cuteness.
I crossed that out because I felt
like my fans would get upset.
It's too much to look at.
It's too much to look at?
That's why I crossed it out.
I shouldn't do this here.
But...
- Do you have a new version?
- A new version?
Where should I look?
Despicable cuteness. 1, 2, 3.
(Sounding so nasally)
(We are we embarrassed for her?)
(Nasally)
This studio is too cold for Ji Soo.
(I can't watch this)
So can you hold me?
I'd love it if you held me.
Hold on. That was all good but
why are you laughing so much,
sound director?
(LOL)
I was shocked.
I bet your fans would love that.
That was actually very cute.
That was adorable.
Can anyone else be despicably cute?
Mi Joo.
Mi Joo, let's see.
- Please no!
- Mi Joo.
Hmph! I don't know how to act cute!
(She loses her mind!)
What? What was that?
She was a despicable monster.
- DM.
So funny...
They were really cute.
They weren't despicable.
Ji Soo, you really like rock music.
What's your favorite band?
I like the Arctic Monkeys
and Blur.
Mostly British bands.
Yes, I like British bands.
I love rock too.
I heard you showed off
your drumming skills recently.
Really?
I had a solo performance for our concert.
I decided to show people my drumming.
You learned how to play the drums?
I did but less than 10 lessons.
It was less than 10 lessons...
I bet you practiced hard since
it was for your concert.
I just learned the basics.
(Modest and embarrassed)
Still not easy to learn
in less than 10 lessons.
That's why... We prepared this.
Show them.
What's that?
(We prepared this just for Ji Soo)
A full drum kit.
For real.
- Actual drums.
- We prepared a lot.
I love rock music too,
so I really want to see this.
The bass.
How do I do this?
- Just play however you like.
- Do whatever you want.
Just do what you want.
Freestyle.
- Go?
- She looks so cool.
So cool.
I'm so nervous.
(Serious)
(Let's watch Ji Soo play the drums)
(Drumming)
(This girl is so cool!)
(Bravo, Ji Soo)
She's good.
- Can you play what you just played.
- So cool.
Are you going to rap?
(Ji Soo's drumming with
Sang Min's crying rap)
(So cute)
Ji Soo's drum and my rapping!
Okay, okay.
Let's get it!
Lovelyz is on Weekly Idol!
(Oh! Oh!)
Come on!
(The other hosts are embarrassed)
(Shin Young is dying)
(Please stop...)
You're not supposed to laugh at me!
(But you were so funny!)
I'm not joking here...
(Ow, my stomach)
Oh, my stomach...
(The embarrassment won't go away...)
There are old guys like that
on "Korea Sings."
There are guys like him.
(Cracking up)
Guys just come on and start singing...
Ji Soo, that was great.
(Ji Soo's good at the drums)
10 lessons of drumming.
- Amazing.
- I'm embarrassed.
Next.
Jin!
She can sing any song like a ballad.
- Nice.
- That's hard.
I don't do this because I want to.
But no matter what song I sing,
the composers say it sounds like a ballad.
Really?
That's when I realized I could sing
any song like a ballad.
Shall we hear her then?
Let's start with a dance song.
- "Ah-Choo."
(How will she sing this bubbly song?)
♪ Ah-choo ♪
♪ Seeing you makes me want to sneeze ♪
♪ I have many things I want to tell you ♪
That last part.
A lot of grooving and breathing.
Right, the way you breathe...
Such a different groove.
Can you sing a trot song
like a ballad?
A trot song?
- "Oh My."
- That sounds good.
5, 6, 7, 8.
♪ Oh my, oh my ♪
♪ Please don't do this ♪
♪ A woman's heart changes frequently ♪
(She can really sing any song like a ballad)
She's good at singing.
Next, let's look at Ye In!
The youngest. Ye In.
If you look at Ji Soo's chemistry
with the members...
"Ye In has the sexy body that I want."
That's what she wrote.
What part of her body do you want?
All of it.
All of it?
She's slim yet firm.
She's been dancing since she was a kid.
All I did was play computer games as a kid.
(A sudden confession)
I just played computer games.
So I'm really envious of how firm she is.
I want her body.
Do you agree?
She's always telling me how
jealous she is of my body.
It's not that nice but
she keeps saying that.
You seem happy about this.
Well, it is nice.
All girls like hearing that.
Do you think about it when you're
walking in front of Ji Soo?
A bit.
Ye In also put on a special performance
during their concert.
- Yes...
- What did you do?
I danced to Park Ji Yoon's "Coming of Age."
Now that I'm 21...
Unless you have a nice figure,
that dance looks weird.
- You'll seem like Psy.
- For real.
Can you dance here?
Can we see it?
This is...
Do you have the song?
- We have all the songs.
- We have Park Ji Yoon backstage.
Ji Yoon!
(She's laughing a lot today!)
I don't remember. Oh, no.
Just relax.
I don't remember the dance.
(Transforms)
(She doesn't remember but her body does...)
(Kei is embarrassed)
(I am no longer a little girl)
The highlight.
(Shaking)
(Ye In just made history with that dance)
That was funny.
The pride of Okcheon. Mi Joo.
She wrote this as her skill. Silly dancing.
Let's see her silly dancing.
Can you show us?
There's a silly dancer amongst us too.
Se Yoon!
I've never done a silly dance here.
I feel like I'll lose because...
I've never been funny by dancing.
Cue the music.
Who dances first?
(Looks so relaxed)
- She's good.
- She's too good!
- Go, Se Yoon!
- Go! Go!
(Flapping)
What was that?
(She can make dance moves to any song)
What is this?
How can I beat that?
(Chaotic)
Protect Mi Joo.
How can I beat that?
Mi Joo needs to be protected.
She had her feet like this!
How did you walk like this?
Did you learn ballet?
(I'll show you)
How can I beat that?
Goodness...
Keep going since it's a battle.
- Can't I just watch?
- No, no.
- How do I beat that?
- Cue the music.
How do I beat that?
(She changes whenever she hears music)
How are you doing that with your feet?
Mi Joo.
Your turn, Se Yoon.
(An homage of Mi Joo)
(Trying his best)
(Leg lift!)
Don't, Mi Joo!
(How about this?)
(Sheesh, Mi Joo)
Cue the music.
("Monkey Magic" by Lee Park Sa)
(She can dance to any genre)
You can't beat her.
How is she doing this?
(Mi Joo...)
Cue the music.
What's this?
("Ring Ring" by Kim Young Chul)
(A dancing master doesn't blame the music)
Hold on. Time out.
(This dancing machine can't be stopped)
Mi Joo, time out.
Hold on, hold on.
Sorry, but she needs protection.
Mi Joo is the top dancer here.
She's the best.
The one who made the legendary clip here.
It's Kei.
She wrote flower for all of them.
This is her opinion.
All the members see you as a flower.
Only Mi Joo is the fan.
A fan of what?
I'm a fan of "Rilakkuma."
I'm a fan of the cartoon.
You have a bunch of dolls?
I have a bunch in my room.
Which Mi Joo doesn't really like.
She said she doesn't annoy people.
Unbelievable...
- I have something to say.
- What is it?
Hold on.
Okay, okay.
Cue the music!
Talk as you dance.
I have something to say.
I don't like dolls.
(Sorry...)
I couldn't believe my ears.
I don't like dolls.
Half the space in our room...
Is taken up by dolls.
Our room is split in half.
Our furniture is different too.
Our styles are totally different.
You wrote that the other members
will think of you as a flower.
Lovelyz, you think she's a flower?
Yes.
Really? Thank you.
We have to see what kind of flower Kei is.
Does she really have a flower face?
We should see if she has a flower face.
The rest of you should sing.
Start.
♪ Kei is blooming in Lovelyz ♪
What kind of flower?
Rapeseed blossom.
(This is a rapeseed blossom)
Sing the song.
♪ Kei is blooming in Lovelyz ♪
What kind of flower?
- Cherry blossom.
(This is a cherry blossom)
♪ Kei is blooming in Lovelyz ♪
A pasqueflower.
(Such a cute pasqueflower...)
What kind of flower?
A plum blossom.
(Sexy plum blossom)
♪ Kei is blooming in Lovelyz ♪
Camellia flower.
That's enough.
It's fine.
- This is so hard.
- It's always Kei.
So... I was right.
It was Kei in that legendary clip
that started it all.
Every girl group after you did that.
(They've all tried it)
(Peek-a-boo)
That was quite the meme.
(Right)
Cue the music.
(Peek-a-boo)
(In a different class)
(They all watch the originator)
(The old guys are loving this...)
(A perfect finish)
(Her cuteness can make you forget
all your troubles)
So different.
They have such good chemistry
as they watch each other.
- They watched like this.
- Like this.
They make her a flower.
(Watching Kei like flowers...)
Now let's move on to the 8th one.
The last one.
We've waited a long time.
Su Jeong!
Ryu Su Jeong!
Chubby cheeks.
Singing, playing with slime...
Making faces on stage.
What is the face you make the most
on stage?
I smile a lot.
- Smiling.
- That's hard.
You always look like you took
a sip of soda.
Right, I make that face a lot.
Right? She does that a lot.
(Kyah)
That face...
We have someone that can
contort his face any way he wants.
We have someone amazing here.
A face that moves freely.
Yoo Se Yoon!
- The facequalizer.
- Right, the facequalizer.
Take a look.
(This is amazing just to watch...)
(LOL)
He can express any song with his face.
(Ji Ae tries to copy him)
Okay, wasn't that funny?
We have to see Su Jeong try this.
- Can you do this?
- Let's see it.
The faecqualizer.
We prepared the interlude
of a Lovelyz song.
(Su Jeong, you're quite the girl)
(What was that?)
(So bubbly)
(Her facequalizer looks pretty good)
She's good at winking.
(Embarrassed)
(She's good!)
She's good.
It's her song.
(Is this the tonguequalizer?)
She kept using her tongue
because of Se Yoon.
She shouldn't have watched his.
Su Jeong needs protection.
It had quite the impact.
- She's good.
- Yeah.
Very good.
I should've prepared something.
No, no. You didn't have to.
So that was Show Yourself.
Don't forget to tune in every
Wednesday at 6! Weekly Idol!
Weekly Idol Arcade!
Lovelyz can do anything they want.
You can play whatever game you want.
5 out of 8 of them wrote
the same game in their Self-Written Report.
Bad lip reading!
You know the rules to this game, right?
You can't hear your voices...
This should be fun!
You can only read lips and gestures.
The last person must guess right.
You have 10 questions and 3 minutes.
For every one you get right,
they get a snack.
I know you all want to eat.
We have 8 snacks.
We have chicken feet, pork hocks...
Pizza, fried chicken...
If you guess wrong, we'll be eating
the remaining food.
We really don't want to eat.
But we have no choice.
You go last.
Baby Soul.
Su Jeong?
Su Jeong will go last?
You tell me.
The music should be loud.
You can't hear each other, right?
(Can you hear, Mi Joo?)
(She's just enjoying the music)
Mi Joo is excited.
They're ready.
My ears really hurt.
(First word: Ganggang sullae)
Ganggang sullae.
(Silent)
Let's go, Juliet?
(How'd she make the term longer?)
Ganggang sullae.
(She gets it)
(Right on the mark)
Ganggang sullae.
One more time.
(She grabs her and says it again)
Ganggang sullae.
(Nods)
(Peek-a-boo)
Gang...
Ga!
Ganggang sullae.
Hug you?
(Warm)
(Causes a heart attack)
(Still don't know?)
Ganggang sullae!
(Ding dong, Kei)
Just mouth it out.
Gang.
Ganggang sullae!
- Moon.
- Full moon.
Ganggang sullae! Ganggang sullae!
(Ganggang sullae)
(Can't get through to her)
On a full moon do the ganggang sullae!
(Let's just dance!)
(Now it's become charades)
Ganggang sullae!
(Kei is pleased)
(They're having fun with this)
Ganggang sullae!
(Baby Soul watches Mi Joo hop around)
(One more time)
The full moon! Peek-a-boo!
(They all watch Mi Joo)
She's doing it all.
(Staring)
(She doesn't care as long as she's excited)
(Pressured...)
Ganggang sullae!
(We thought Mi Joo would do well...)
(She's a true variety show gem)
No! No!
(No!)
(5 characters?)
No! Hold on.
Tell us. Tell me what it is.
Ganggang suwollae!
Yeah, I think you got it.
That's not how you say it.
(Loudly)
Ganggang suwollae!
- Ganggang suwollae?
- Ganggang suwollae.
Ganggang suwollae? Ganggang sullae.
(Huh?)
Wasn't that right?
(Trying to figure things out)
You said suwollae.
Hurry and do the next one!
You don't have time!
- Hold on.
- Let's do this.
- Turn around.
- Let's do a hard one.
(Iodine solution)
(What is that?)
This is a good one.
Iodine solution.
What?
- I...
- Do...
- O...
- Yo...
Yo!
- Dine...
- Ji...
So...
Lu...
- So, so...
- Ji...
So...
She's stubborn.
(They're just dancing)
(Ye In dances to the rhythm)
(Still stuck!)
Iodine.
(Still stuck on one syllable)
Dine.
- Iodine.
- Solution.
- Yeah.
- Iodine. Yeah.
- Solu...
- Iodine what?
(3 minutes ended a long time ago...)
- Iodine smell.
- Keep going.
- You're short on time.
I...
Iodine smell.
(Jin is the black hole)
Huh?
Iodine smell.
(It sounds so weird)
(No idea)
- What are you saying?
- Keep going.
Keep going.
(One more time)
(Keeps saying the wrong answer)
(Back)
(Jin's wrong answer)
(Acting silly)
Keep going.
Ji Ae, keep going.
(Just go!)
(Gives up)
Ro?
Dol?
Loco?
Iodine smell!
(Watching)
(Iodine solution, iodine smell, dolphin cry)
Dolphin cry.
Iodine smell.
Dolphin?
(I should watch from up close)
(Jin changes the wrong answer)
Iodine scent.
Iodine.
Iodine scent. What is that?
(Tries not to laugh!)
The clock is ticking.
(You guys ran out of time long ago)
Keep going.
Lumbar...
Iodine smell.
(Serious)
Keep going.
- One more time.
- Hurry up and just go.
Hurry up and just go.
(Tell me)
Lum...
Lumbar...
(The first one in line can only laugh...)
- Lumbar.
- Lumbar?
Lumbar?
System?
(Now it's lumbar system?)
Lumbar system.
- That's what they're saying?
- System.
System.
- Lumbar system.
- Keep going!
I have no idea.
(So excited)
Ah-choo.
♪ Ah-choo ♪
Lumbar.
System.
(They're stuck on system...)
- Huh?
- I'm not sure.
She did this...
Yo, ah-choo. What's this?
I don't know either.
What's the word?
Lumbar.
(Is there even such a word?)
Yo, ah-choo, bang!
Bang!
(That's what she did)
(An explanation with hip hop and K-Pop)
Bang.
I don't know.
(This is nuts)
What's this?
- You don't know?
- I don't know.
Just keep going.
Keep going.
Yo...
(They're like rappers now)
Ah-choo.
(Promoting their song)
Choo?
Ah-choo.
Bang!
That's...
Yo, ah-choo...
- Bang.
- Bang?
(Now it's yo ah-choo bang)
What's the answer?
This time next year?
Yo ah-choo bang?
(Nope)
The answer is iodine solution.
Iodine solution.
(My snacks)
I said iodine smell.
Iodine smell.
We gave you 10 minutes.
We didn't get a single one.
Let's just do this.
They really want to eat but
the questions were too hard.
We'll change the order and give
you another chance.
How should we change it up?
I'll stay in the center.
But you can suddenly change the answer.
(Wrongly accused)
At least I got iodine right.
If you get this one right,
you get 3 snacks.
Get ready. Start.
(Mind goes blank)
Mind goes blank.
(Rushing)
- Mind blank.
Mind goes blank.
(They get it right)
Turn around.
Mind goes blank.
(I got it!)
(They're on the right track so far)
Okay, they're fast.
(Jin is next)
Mind...
I'll stay in the center.
(Jin acted like she was the best one)
(How will she do?)
Mind goes blank.
(Super focused)
Metal?
Mind, mind.
Goes blank.
- Goes blank.
- Goes black.
(Can't get through to her)
Mind goes blank.
(You're not the best at this Jin...)
(Can't communicate)
Turn around.
- Mind goes blank.
(Jin is no longer the black hole!)
Mind...
Goes blank.
(So tactful)
She knows.
(Looks like we'll get this
and get a snack)
(How will dancing Mi Joo do?)
Mind...
Mi Joo knows?
Half moon.
- Brain. Mind.
- Half moon.
Mind. Mind.
Half moon.
(Her mind is going blank for real)
Mind goes blank!
We need someone like this.
Half moon goes blank.
Turn around.
Mind, mind.
(Please!)
Turn around.
Goes blank.
Half moon split?
Turn around.
(Oh, no)
Heo Cham would love her.
Half moon goes blank.
(Clapping)
Mind goes blank.
(Su Jeong seems so cool right now)
That was unexpected.
(What's the answer?)
(Nervous)
Mind goes blank.
Correct!
(So excited)
You got one right so you
get 3 snacks.
3.
(They forget about their victory!)
It's wasteful to just eat this.
Let's eat the pizza.
Let's eat the total opposite.
Spicy rice cakes.
No, they got cold.
We need meat.
The pork hocks.
They're so serious.
- Should we eat squid?
- We've decided.
You did? What? Pizza, pork hocks...
And squid stir-fry.
You can eat those 3 snacks.
Congratulations!
Thank you for the food.
Eat up.
It's so good.
(Just watching them eat makes us full...)
(Nom)
This is good.
Thank you.
Lovelyz are lovely no matter what.
This is the Network Quiz!
We changed things up a bit.
The winner will get to give these
dolls to your fans.
(Lovelyz will try for their fans!)
(I'll win 1st!)
(So determined)
No.
A goddess like Mi Joo...
Wrong!
(Thinking of their fans!)
(I'll get this right!)
I know what this is!
You're almost there!
It's multiple choice.
- We have up to 74 choices.
- Su Jeong!
Su Jeong.
- 12. Yellow dust.
- 12. Yellow dust?
14. Yellow dust.
Ye In!
Ye In.
Hunseok.
Correct!
(Ye In is really killing it)
Ye In.
I want to eat raw fish.
Correct!
(I just do what I do!)
This means Ye In wins
and she gets 100 dolls for her fans!
(The winner of the Network Quiz is Ye In)
Since Ye In won...
How about a message to your fans?
Fans, I hope you cherish these dolls
and take them to bed as you think of me!
Okay!
It's time to end our show for today.
We had so much fun.
- Did you have fun?
- So much fun!
What a relief.
I feel like we got closer over
that brief period.
People say how lovely you girls are.
Now I can see it too.
(Thank you)
So awkward...
I'll scratch my head.
Let's wrap things up.
- Whether it's here...
- Or there...
In the end... Weekly Idol!
Please give "That Day" lots of love.
Lovelyz.
(They're so lovely powerful)
(Thank you for your positive energy, Lovelyz!)
(We'll see you again next episode)
Good work, girls.
("That Night" by Lovelyz)