Well, now we have last...
Three songs.
I know it's sad.
Please pour all your energy left to our last three songs, okay?
YES!!
Then, let's go to the next song.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
♪ When I first met you ♫
♪ It was a little earlier than what you remember ♫
♪ I always secretly looked at you from behind ♫
♪ You wouldn’t really know ♫
♪ If I were to be honest ♫
♪ Will my frustrated heart feel relieved? ♫
♪ If I tell you everything ♫
♪ What if things get awkward? ♫
♪ I look in the mirror ♫
♪ Count to one ♫
♪ Count to two, then say Hi~ ♫
♪ Do you want to meet? I have something to tell you ♫
♪ Let’s meet because I have something to ask you ♫
♪ I’m saying this with courage ♫
♪ So please answer me honestly ♫
♪ Do you want to meet? I’ve waited for a long time ♫
♪ Let’s meet, not just as friends ♫
♪ Hey, you see, I really love you ♫
♪ I endlessly practiced ♫
♪ But I can’t help it, my heart is trembling ♫
♪ What do I do? I keep getting scared ♫
♪ If I have to do it, I should do it quickly ♫
♪ I’ll call you ♫
♪ Count to one ♫
♪ Count to two, then say Hi~ ♫
♪ Do you want to meet? I have something to tell you ♫
♪ Let’s meet because I have something to ask you ♫
♪ I’m saying this with courage ♫
♪ So please answer me honestly ♫
♪ Do you want to meet? I’ve waited for a long time ♫
♪ Let’s meet, not just as friends ♫
♪ Hey, you see, I really love you ♫
♪ This minute, this second of this moment ♫
♪ Feels longer than yesterday ♫
♪ Don’t just smile but say something ♫
♪ Stop doing that, what’s so funny? ♫
♪ Stop doing that, I’m serious here ♫
♪ I’m saying this with courage ♫
♪ So please answer me honestly ♫
♪ Do you want to meet? I’ve waited for a long time ♫
♪ Let’s meet, not just as friends ♫
♪ Hey, you see, I really love you ♫
♪ I found someone ♫
♪ I’d like to make good food for ♫
♪ I’m not very good at cooking ♫
♪ But I’m working on it ♫
♪ I even have hidden talents just for you ♫
♪ Like cute charms ♫
♪ You’ll never be bored, I’ll make you laugh ♫
♪ But you have no idea ♫
♪ Ah Choo! ♫
♪ I feel like sneezing when I see you ♫
♪ There are so many things I wanna tell you ♫
♪ My lips tickle, it’s hard holding back ♫
♪ Ah Choo! ♫
♪ Flowers must be blooming in my heart ♫
♪ There are so many things I wanna do for you ♫
♪ My feelings, this love for you is hard to contain ♫
♪ I found someone ♫
♪ I’d like to wake in the morning ♫
♪ I like to sleep in ♫
♪ But won’t mind getting up early ♫
♪ When I see you feeling down, I feel sad too ♫
♪ I’ll be there whenever you need me ♫
♪ But you have no idea ♫
♪ Ah Choo! ♫
♪ I feel like sneezing when I see you ♫
♪ There are so many things I wanna tell you ♫
♪ My lips tickle, it’s hard holding back ♫
♪ Ah Choo! ♫
♪ Flowers must be blooming in my heart ♫
♪ There are so many things I wanna do for you ♫
♪ My feelings, this love for you is hard to contain ♫
♪ When you call me a good friend ♫
♪ I really like it ♫
♪ Unfinished letters I write all night ♫
♪ Love I haven’t confessed yet ♫
♪ Ah Choo! ♫
♪ I feel like sneezing when I see you ♫
♪ There are so many things I wanna tell you ♫
♪ My lips tickle, it’s hard holding back ♫
♪ Ah Choo! ♫
♪ Flowers must be blooming in my heart ♫
♪ There are so many things I wanna do for you ♫
♪ My feelings, this love for you is hard to contain ♫
♪ Why aren’t I waking up? ♫
♪ I always wake up right about now ♫
♪ I’m not saying I don’t like it ♫
♪ It’s just not hitting me, to be honest ♫
♪ Why are you softly holding my hand and whispering to me? ♫
♪ I don’t know, I can’t hear anything ♫
♪ You’re too close ♫
♪ The whole world is spinning, I’m dizzy ♫
♪ Right now, you and I, everything seems unreal ♫
♪ Each minute with you feels unreal ♫
♪ Is this a dream? Or not? I feel hazy ♫
♪ You say that you like me ♫
♪ What do I do? I guess this is for real ♫
♪ We’re walking under the light ♫
♪ Round and round, my eyes follow you ♫
♪ I’m lightly trying to match my steps with yours ♫
♪ I guess this is real ♫
♪ I guess we’re gonna be lovers ♫
♪ I think I’m running out of breath ♫
♪ Not saying this awkwardness is bad ♫
♪ That loving look ♫
♪ It resembles me looking at you ♫
♪ I slightly opened my eyes ♫
♪ And measured the distance between us ♫
♪ There’s only one inch left ♫
♪ We might touch soon ♫
♪ The whole world is spinning, I’m dizzy ♫
♪ Right now, you and I, everything seems unreal ♫
♪ Each minute with you feels unreal ♫
♪ Is this a dream? Or not? I feel hazy ♫
♪ You say that you like me ♫
♪ What do I do? I guess this is for real ♫
♪ We’re walking under the light ♫
♪ Round and round, my eyes follow you ♫
♪ I’m lightly trying to match my steps with yours ♫
♪ I guess this is real ♫
♪ I guess we’re gonna be lovers ♫
♪ The melody that started in my ear ♫
♪ I countlessly drew this out ♫
♪ Your trembling, my fluttering ♫
♪ We’re dancing in a soft pink light ♫
♪ You and I being this close seems unreal ♫
♪ Your heart ringing like crazy seems unreal ♫
♪ Is this a dream? Or not? I feel hazy ♫
♪ You say that you love me ♫
♪ What do I do? I guess this is for real ♫
♪ We’re walking under the light ♫
♪ Round and round, my eyes follow you ♫
♪ I’m lightly trying to match my steps with yours ♫
♪ I guess this is real ♫
♪ I guess we’re gonna be lovers ♫
Hello LOVELINUS, I'm Baby Soul >-<
The eight of us will always be by your side like you've been for us.
Thank you, we love you ❤ Let's be together forever ❤❤
We will always sing by LOVELINUS side ❤
LOVELINUS, promise us you will always be with LOVELYZ >_<
Thank you always!! I love you ❤3❤
We will always be together, bbyong ❤
LOVELINUS~ Thank you for being always by my side.
The reason I sing is LOVELINUS.
I will be e asinger who make you proud. Thank you.
Hello, I'm LOVELYZ's MiJoo ❤
Thank you so much for being next to LOVELYZ always.
Please, remember our memories of the second concert 'ALWAYZ'.
I wish we could always be together >_<
LOVELYZ and LOVELINUS will be always together.
I'll love you forever ❤ ❤  From MiJoo...❤
Oh~ What's going on? ❤
Do you know how much I missed you?
Why, why! I'm not lying.
I love LOVELINUS so much ❤
This much~ This much~ This much~
I really~ like you chu, chu ❤
To. LOVELINUS~ ❤3❤
LOVELINUS~ Hi~!! I'm YeIn >__<!!
I will never forget the love from LOVELINUS that I'll never receive again in my life and I'll be the one that grows up every moment with you.
I love you, LOVELINUS❤ ❤ ❤  100% filled with love.
1. Always and forever (LOVELYZ❤LOVELINUS)
2. (Remember) always (LOVELIZ❤LOVELINUS)
3. (In the future) until forever (LOVELYZ❤LOVELINUS)
Just as always [like always]
(LOVELYZ❤LOVELINUS)
Do you remember our first concert?
We cried, laughed and made memories together.
We will make you unforgettable memories on July of 2017.