- Hello!
- Peek-a-boo!
- LOVELINUS!
- Hello!
Nice to meet you.
Ah, we...
Performed 'Candy Jelly Love' differently from yesterday.
'Candy Jelly Love'...
Singing 'Candy Jelly love' again...
Makes me feel we must start over the concert.
It feels like it's the opening again.
Let's do it again,let's do it again.
- Shall we do it again?
- Shall we?
- I wan to do it again.
We did an encore song and then it's really over.
We are going to talk about our thoughts o being with LOVELINUS at a big concert all. One by one.
- Starting from YeIn today,
- Yes, from the youngest member.
Red beans...
I will try hard to become Red beans.
Everyone, it's really the last moment of today's ALWAYZ concert.
How can this happen?
I can't believe this...
Being first is more pressuring than I thought,
I don't know what I should say first.
First of all, thank you so much for filling up our second concert too.
But I won't cry.
I didn't cry yesterday.
I'm not crying, I'm not crying.
I won't cry today.
I kept saying thank you so much yesterday,
so I don't want to end my ment by keep saying thank you again.
This is what I thought.
The time we didn't perform on stage after 'Now, We',
it made me imagine that one day we will become grandmothers.
And when time passes, I might not be able
to sing in front of LOVELINUS or other people.
So this moment is so overwhelming and very honoring.
The two days were so valuable and happy.
That made me think that I was born to do this.
And there are many people who make a difficult debut through TV programs.
They make me think about lots of things.
LOVELINUS, you are such a happiness that make me forget all the hardships.
So don't go anywhere and stay by my side even tough I'm not perfect.
Working with these cool members and staffs,
and meeting LOVELINUS is such a blessing in my life.
And these days are totally unforgettable.
Actually,
when I first started LOVELYZ,
I thought a lot about 'Who would like me?'
Because I didn't have anything.
Umh, so...
Thank you.
So actually this...
The moment I'm standing here
feels like a dream.
And I'll call our pink lightstick the 'Lovebong'.
This lightstick...
Being waved makes this place look like it's real night and you look like stars.
Because every one of you is shinning so much.
Everyone, let's glitter and shine each other. Even in the future, just like we do now.
That's how I want us to be together. And...
Thank you to my parents who came to the concert for two days in a row.
I wish my grandmother's and my aunt's health
I want everyone to be healthy.
I want everyone here to be healthy.
Thank you to my friends too.
I didn't say it before bu thank you Young Jun for being here.
But he ones who watch me from far
and lead me whenever I am depressed or in trouble,
and the ones whom I am most grateful is you who are here now.
I really, really, think a lot about you.
So don't go anywhere else and I want to be with you forever. I love you so much.
Ah, thank you.
LOVELYZ's ALWAYZ concert
which we have been waiting for so long is finally happily and joyfully over now.
While preparing for the concert, I thought and felt many things,
but first of all, thank you to our CEO who helps us to be able to perform on stages every time.
And I want to thank you LOVELINUS for being the reason of our stage.
There are our lacking parts when we practice.
We are worried about what we should do with those problems,
but when we come up on stage,
LOVELINUS helps us not think about it anymore.
And you are the ones who make us believe that we are doing so well.
So thank you for giving us energy on stage
and giving us the reason to be powerful.
Just like YeIn said, you are really like stars.
I've said this before at the last concert.
When the lights go out, you wave the lovebongs just like now,
and everytime you do, I'm so happy as if I'm dreaming.
I am so proud.
We will try hard to become proud singers,
so will you cheer for us forever?
YES!!
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much for filling up the seats.
And I wish we could be together for the next and the upcoming concerts and enjoy together.
Yes, LOVELINUS, thank you so much.
I made a tongueslip to you yesterday.
I said I didn't have friends.
What I was trying to say wasn't that.
I was...
trying to express the loneliness of my heart.
But I think I said it in a wrong way.
I invited my friends. I invited 20 friends yesterday,
and 20 friends again today. So I'm the 1st among the members.
But...
You are my friends too.
So I hope you aren't upset about it.
And thank you to our CEO who helped us stand here.
Chairman Hunseok, chairman YoungJun,
vice-president JiYoung, and all the Woollim staffs, thank you,
Ah, I almost forgot. Thank you SeHee.
Since LOVELINUS exists,
I exist too.
I know it's obvious,
but I think my true heart is all said.
Even at the last concert too!
So I really...
There are so many things that I still haven't shown to LOVELINUS yet.
But I have more days to live, don't I?
And you do too.
I will be a singer until the day I live.
LOVELYZ, we will be always together!
LOVELINUS, you'll always be LOVELINUS too.
I won't speed up during the time given.
I'm going to take it slow,
so I'll be to LOVELINUS, th JIN who slowly improves, and...
Thank you to my parents who cheer me,
cheer me,
pray for me, and praise me for doing well.
Thank you to my parents and my sister JooEun.
I won't cry. I am really strong now.
I got really strong during this summer so I won't cry.
I always said...
that I'll be strong and
said 'I'm older than you' to the younger members,
but I think I was a kid until now.
So starting from today,
I know it's too late, but from today,
I will be a strong elder sister.
I want LOVELINUS to watch that.
What?
Fighting!
Thank you so much until now.
As a member of LOVELYZ,
as JIN, the singer,
and as a person Park MyungEun,
I will try to become a good person, a right person.
Watch me. Thank you.
I wanted to thank everyone who came to the concert.
Thank you.
I got more confident trough yesterday's concert.
So today, I really threw myself to the stage.
So I enjoyed it so much and I was really happy.
Because of you, the stages were so happy.
And I thank LOVELINUS for making me to improve everyday.
I will try to give you bigger energy and a brighter energy.
Everyone, thank you so much.
Yes?
Thank you.
And Woollim staff.
When we prepare for our concert, the whole company gets so busy.
All of you must be tired, and you did a great job.
Thank you so much for taking care of us.
And...
our CEO who is sometimes friendly but sometimes difficult.
When we are having a hard time.
Lee Joon Yeop! Lee Joon Yeop! Lee Joon Yeop!
God-Joon Yeop.
Everytime we are having a hard time, he supports us.
and thank you for giving us the courage, CEO.
We could be on this stage because of you, I love you.
I love all the Woollim staffs,
and the band, and other staffs, you've done a great job today.
Thank you so much.
Today is a really special day.
My family is here.
They are cheering me over there.
Mom, they are thanking you!
When I was young and I just vaguely said 'Mom, I want to be a singer',
when I just said 'I want to be a singer',
She just...
didn't disagree at all and kept supporting me
and cheering me.
So I think...
I am at this place because of my parents.
I love my family so much.
I will also become a star that only shines for LOVELINUS.
LOVELINUS should
always, always, always
look at
LOVELYZ only.
YES!!!
Thank you, I love you.
I won't cry today.
Thank you for coming to our concert for two days in a row.
I lost track of what I said yesterday because I was crying,
and so I won't cry today in order to thank you properly.
Yesterday...
I saw the video of me talking.
And I thought 'How stupid can I be?'
I kept saying I'm going to be mature,
but watching me talking makes me think I was so stupid.
I kept crying and couldn't even talk properly.
So today I will...
Ah, what?
Thank you.
What?
Was I cute?
First of all, the glittering stars! are the ones who made us able to dance and sing on the stage.
Thank you so much.
LOVELINUS are the one who solve the problem when LOVELYZ has one.
So when you have problems, talk to us.
We have a show about troubles.
And we are always open.
We are always open,
so come to us, okay?
Thank you so much for shining like this all the time, LOVELINUS.
The amazing thing is how could we think about the same thing?
SuJeong and YeIn.
Stars, you are really like stars.
You really shine.
I felt at the first concert.
- Lightsticks! Pink stars.
- Stars.
Thank you very much for completing the two days of ALWAYZ concert.
And thank you to the band who must have had a hard time,
and thank you to all the Woollim staffs.
Please take care of LOVELYZ in the future too.
Yes, I didn't cry today.
Well done!
Pat, pat, pat.
Yes, it's me.
They said everything before me, so I don't know what to say.
But I'll say what pops up in my head.
More fans are here today than yesterday.
Thank you for enjoying it energetically with us.
And because of you, our performances got complete.
In the future, I would like to enjoy stages with you
at a bigger stage.
I'm grateful to all the staffs, but they already said it.
So I won't do it.
But I hope you will know that I'm thankful.
Um, and...
What?
Firm. Yes, I am firm.
And my family is here too.
My mother came to the 'LOVELYZ in Winterland' too.
At 'LOVELYZ in Winterland', when I was doing to closing ment,
I didn't talk about my family. I was out of my mind and I forgot.
My mom came to me and said
'Why didn't you talk about me when the other members talked about their family'
'I'm so upset'. So this time I'm going to say it.
But mom... mom, thank you...
for giving birth to me.
The reason I could be a singer was
Don't cry! Don't cry! Don't cry!
Thank you.
She said thank you.
The reason I could be a singer was...
My mom and my family...
Don't cry, you fool.
I think it was because I had a family.
It's not like I didn't want to say it
I forgot.
It's alright! It's alright! It's alright!
I want to thank my mom,
my sister and my family.
We have three cats at home, and I thank them too.
But the most grateful ones are you, LOVELINUS.
I'm not good at expressing,
but I'm grateful. So grateful.
What I felt during the concert was that
we do not want to die while we live,
but we die anyway.
Who would experience this while we live?
There aren't many people who can perform in front of many people.
I feel so grateful,
and I think it's such a valuable experience.
Let's make more good memories.
And I stop LOVELYZ members talking and emcee al the time,
but thank you
and I want to say that I love you all.
It's your turn.
Well.
Well, as previously mentioned, Woollim Family,
the staffs, the band, and Big Picture Performance team.
Thank you so much once again.
But LOVELINUS is who I thank the most.
Well just... I always think of
the last comment...
but I don't know what to say.
Because I always thank you.
Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry!
I always feel like I want to say that I love you,
and saying only good things, but they are too short.
They are short, so...
Everytime before I stand on stage...
this is what I think.
I'm...
nothing...
and nobody...
But the love you constantly give me
and cheer for me...
is just too much for me.
To you...
When you give us 100,
I want to give you 200, 300 and more.
But I'm always so sorry that I'm lacking of everything.
Really...
I want to say thank you and I love you for supporting me.
And filling up this place.
My mom and sister are here too.
But the 'LOVELYZ in Winterland'
Those who came to the winter concert will know
that I said I don't cry in front of my family.
I did...
But today,
I cried because there were so many things to be sorry and thankful to all of you.
I will be better for you,
and be the JiSoo who can return more than I receive.
So let's please meet for a long time.
Yes!!!
I love you.
Yes, it's my turn~
All the members cried before me.
Oh no!
Well, my parents also came here today.
The piano sounds so great.
When I was singing 'Candy Jelly Love' as the encore song,
I was eye contacting with the fans, and saw my mother all of sudden...
like 'boom'. And so I said 'hi' and went.
I saw her.
My heart was beating like boom!
But at that time,
Since 'Candy Jelly Love' was an encore song for LOVELINUS...
so I focused more for LOVELINUS.
But thank you to my parents for coming,
thank you for supporting all the time.
And for the first time, my high school friends are here at the concert.
Thank you so much for coming.
Okcheon, Okcheon, Okcheon.
Yes! Okcheon... Okcheon is good!
Yes, thank you for coming.
And thank you so much for sweating while waiting outside in the heat for our concert.
And since today is the last concert, I feel so sad.
And I feel like I must do it again tomorrow.
Shall we do it again tomorrow?
Well, then.
At 5 pm!
At 5pm?
I want to.
The fact that I became a singer
shouldn't feel like a dream but it still does.
Sometimes it really
feels like a dream.
So I am very scared that I'll go back to reality when I wake up.
But since I have you, LOVELINUS.
You give me the power, and as I said before,
you shine very much.
Wherever you go, 'Oh, you shine!'
Really...
want to see eacho of you with my eyes,
but...
my eyes aren't following me.
I want to see all of you.
I won't cry.
Thank you so much for coming despite this heat.
Your throats are sore from cheering on such a hot day, right?
We are fine!!
Please, don't say you are fine.
You are not fine.
You always go back with sore throats.
And how you can say you are fine?
I know that you aren't.
I shouldn't cry.
But seeing you wave the lovebong so hard.
I know... you are having a hard time.
You are pretty!
Thank you... I look ugly, don't I?
I should look pretty.
It fell down.
MIJOO IS THE PRETTIEST!!!
Thank you, go back home and turn on the air conditioner when you sleep.
Remember to take a shower today.
Those who got wet.
You can smell of sweat because it's hot.
Go home and wash yourself and your clothes.
And dream of LOVELYZ at home.
We will dream of LOVELINUS too.
Thank you for...
cheering up for us like this.
And I hope that we always stay together.
This will not change, same as always.
I look ugly.
I wish that we will always be together.
I love you LOVELINUS,
my parents and CEO Joong Yeop.
I love JiYoung,
I love LOVELINUS,
I love my high school friends,
and I love LOVELYZ.
- Me too!
- We love you too!
Me too.
I love you.
There's something I didn't say.
What is it?
My parents are here too. Even my grandmother.
- Hello.
Today...
Hello!
Hello.
I invited my friends for the first time too.
I'm sorry, my parents are here too...
I love my parents.
And Nini, who always adores me, thank you too.
And there's more things we did'nt say.
We are performing
- ALWAYZ in Japan next week.
- That's right.
Will you support us a lot?
I knew it, LOVELINUS,
- Thank you.
- We will come back safe from Japan.
Then we will end the concert with our final song.
We will sing our next song.
- Bye~
- See you again next time.
Good bye. Good bye.
What's that?
Good bye, I love you.